{
  "26662a02-fb5e-4d0f-a32b-095f1dde9172": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Python Basics (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: Python Basics",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr1f84rg4Nw",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Will Print",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "print",
                "string",
                "written",
                "variable"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And if I am a print C, you will also get print the screen.",
                "But if I have to play a print STR1, then obviously, the string will be printed.",
                "On my print, I will print it on my set.",
                "So, I will accept exception as E. And then I will print the exception.",
                "This is variable which is in the integer variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And if I am a _____ C, you will also get _____ the screen.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "variable",
                    "string",
                    "written"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But if I have to play a _____ STR1, then obviously, the string will be _____ed.",
                  "options": [
                    "string",
                    "will",
                    "variable",
                    "print"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "On my _____, I will _____ it on my set.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "variable",
                    "written",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Type Will",
              "key_points": [
                "type",
                "will",
                "language",
                "tell",
                "strings"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like I am going to say, if I have to run the type D, I will tell you that type is what I have done.",
                "And if you want to convert it to digital, you can get a type of type of type of type.",
                "So, if you are a beginner, then you don't need to do any type of type of type.",
                "I will use the items on the iner nd.. ..and then I will edit 3 tiles\u2026 ..so i can tell that whenever I spend money in one place.. ..to take threat items.",
                "So what is the type of type of type?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like I am going to say, if I have to run the _____ D, I will tell you that _____ is what I have done.",
                  "options": [
                    "strings",
                    "language",
                    "type",
                    "tell"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if you want to convert it to digital, you can get a _____ of _____ of _____ of _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "strings",
                    "type",
                    "tell",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, if you are a beginner, then you don't need to do any _____ of _____ of _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "language",
                    "will",
                    "type",
                    "strings"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "List Will",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "will",
                "change",
                "value",
                "index"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "I will list it on my list or set on my list.",
                "If you define the index in the index, then you will get index equal to 3.",
                "And if you have list of list, then you can list it.",
                "But if you want to change the list of elements, then I have to change it.",
                "And if I have to change my tube value, then I have to change it."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "I will _____ it on my _____ or set on my _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "value",
                    "change",
                    "will",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you define the _____ in the _____, then you will get _____ equal to 3.",
                  "options": [
                    "index",
                    "change",
                    "value",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "index"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if you have _____ of _____, then you can _____ it.",
                  "options": [
                    "change",
                    "index",
                    "will",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Virat",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "virat",
                "value",
                "friend",
                "doing"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "If I have to learn from my friend, Virat will be able to learn from Virat.",
                "If you want to learn from your dictionary, you can learn from your friend.",
                "And if you have a friend, then items And if you have a friend, then you can see that My first element is money.",
                "Virat, jokyam ire ki hai, and his value is a manli jokyam.",
                "Virat is not so much for us to learn from his access."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "If I have to _____ from my friend, Virat will be able to _____ from Virat.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "doing",
                    "friend",
                    "value"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you want to learn from your dictionary, you can learn from your _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "friend",
                    "doing",
                    "virat",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "friend"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if you have a _____, then items And if you have a _____, then you can see that My first element is money.",
                  "options": [
                    "virat",
                    "friend",
                    "learn",
                    "doing"
                  ],
                  "answer": "friend"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Heli",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "heli",
                "want",
                "file",
                "know"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then you will want to do one.TX, and you will want to win the heli.",
                "Now, you will know that, if you have a file, then you will read it.",
                "If you want to make a file, then you will want to write it.",
                "Then i will say a r.write .. And then the heli will make a heli.",
                "If you do that minor to believe you have to close this heli on the heli, Then I will also get to know that."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then you will want to do one.TX, and you will want to win the _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "know",
                    "file",
                    "heli"
                  ],
                  "answer": "heli"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, you will _____ that, if you have a file, then you will read it.",
                  "options": [
                    "heli",
                    "know",
                    "file",
                    "want"
                  ],
                  "answer": "know"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you want to make a _____, then you will want to write it.",
                  "options": [
                    "heli",
                    "will",
                    "want",
                    "file"
                  ],
                  "answer": "file"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "ef4cead5-e701-4658-9a85-77606c3c331c": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Python Basics (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: Python Basics",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr1f84rg4Nw",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Will Print",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "print",
                "string",
                "written",
                "variable"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And if I am a print C, you will also get print the screen.",
                "But if I have to play a print STR1, then obviously, the string will be printed.",
                "On my print, I will print it on my set.",
                "So, I will accept exception as E. And then I will print the exception.",
                "This is variable which is in the integer variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And if I am a _____ C, you will also get _____ the screen.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "print",
                    "variable",
                    "written"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But if I have to play a _____ STR1, then obviously, the string will be _____ed.",
                  "options": [
                    "variable",
                    "will",
                    "print",
                    "written"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "On my _____, I will _____ it on my set.",
                  "options": [
                    "written",
                    "variable",
                    "print",
                    "string"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Type Will",
              "key_points": [
                "type",
                "will",
                "language",
                "tell",
                "strings"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like I am going to say, if I have to run the type D, I will tell you that type is what I have done.",
                "And if you want to convert it to digital, you can get a type of type of type of type.",
                "So, if you are a beginner, then you don't need to do any type of type of type.",
                "I will use the items on the iner nd.. ..and then I will edit 3 tiles\u2026 ..so i can tell that whenever I spend money in one place.. ..to take threat items.",
                "So what is the type of type of type?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like I am going to say, if I have to run the _____ D, I will tell you that _____ is what I have done.",
                  "options": [
                    "tell",
                    "type",
                    "strings",
                    "language"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if you want to convert it to digital, you can get a _____ of _____ of _____ of _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "tell",
                    "will",
                    "strings"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, if you are a beginner, then you don't need to do any _____ of _____ of _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "strings",
                    "type",
                    "language"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "List Will",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "will",
                "change",
                "value",
                "index"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "I will list it on my list or set on my list.",
                "If you define the index in the index, then you will get index equal to 3.",
                "And if you have list of list, then you can list it.",
                "But if you want to change the list of elements, then I have to change it.",
                "And if I have to change my tube value, then I have to change it."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "I will _____ it on my _____ or set on my _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "list",
                    "change",
                    "will",
                    "index"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you define the _____ in the _____, then you will get _____ equal to 3.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "index",
                    "value",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "index"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if you have _____ of _____, then you can _____ it.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "value",
                    "list",
                    "index"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Virat",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "virat",
                "value",
                "friend",
                "doing"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "If I have to learn from my friend, Virat will be able to learn from Virat.",
                "If you want to learn from your dictionary, you can learn from your friend.",
                "And if you have a friend, then items And if you have a friend, then you can see that My first element is money.",
                "Virat, jokyam ire ki hai, and his value is a manli jokyam.",
                "Virat is not so much for us to learn from his access."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "If I have to _____ from my friend, Virat will be able to _____ from Virat.",
                  "options": [
                    "virat",
                    "learn",
                    "doing",
                    "friend"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you want to learn from your dictionary, you can learn from your _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "doing",
                    "value",
                    "friend",
                    "virat"
                  ],
                  "answer": "friend"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if you have a _____, then items And if you have a _____, then you can see that My first element is money.",
                  "options": [
                    "friend",
                    "learn",
                    "virat",
                    "value"
                  ],
                  "answer": "friend"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Heli",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "heli",
                "want",
                "file",
                "know"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then you will want to do one.TX, and you will want to win the heli.",
                "Now, you will know that, if you have a file, then you will read it.",
                "If you want to make a file, then you will want to write it.",
                "Then i will say a r.write .. And then the heli will make a heli.",
                "If you do that minor to believe you have to close this heli on the heli, Then I will also get to know that."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then you will want to do one.TX, and you will want to win the _____.",
                  "options": [
                    "file",
                    "want",
                    "know",
                    "heli"
                  ],
                  "answer": "heli"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, you will _____ that, if you have a file, then you will read it.",
                  "options": [
                    "know",
                    "file",
                    "will",
                    "heli"
                  ],
                  "answer": "know"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you want to make a _____, then you will want to write it.",
                  "options": [
                    "know",
                    "want",
                    "file",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "file"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "3cc8d81f-0b17-478a-8ada-9f641e5585d1": {
    "status": "processing",
    "result": null,
    "error": null
  },
  "76e3c4dc-ec26-4bcf-a57d-921c8949b01e": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "\u001b[0;31mERROR:\u001b[0m Unable to rename file: [WinError 32] The process cannot access the file because it is being used by another process: 'data\\\\audio\\\\fr1f84rg4Nw.webm.part' -> 'data\\\\audio\\\\fr1f84rg4Nw.webm'. Giving up after 3 retries"
  },
  "caeadab6-f452-4db3-9253-ef56bc6f58cd": {
    "status": "processing",
    "result": null,
    "error": null
  },
  "6a7e8342-28cb-44a3-b998-83dbf19d3fe2": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "Transcript not available. Whisper is disabled in API mode."
  },
  "2b37190a-726c-43fe-afb8-c5976a4cfd59": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "Transcript not available. Whisper is disabled in API mode."
  },
  "a1274ac3-62a3-4c25-b166-cb31696e0ae5": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: Deep Learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "will",
                "popular"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you are doing this in deep learning, you will be able to do this.",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been watching deep learning.",
                "In this video, we will talk about the depth of the world."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "will",
                    "learning",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "popular",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you are doing this in _____  learning, you will be able to do this.",
                  "options": [
                    "popular",
                    "deep",
                    "video",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "data",
                "talk",
                "many",
                "when"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that the machine is using.",
                "If you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses and size.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been watching deep learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "many",
                    "learning",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that the machine is using.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "when",
                    "many",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses and size.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "many",
                    "talk",
                    "when"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "features",
                "which",
                "learning"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "As a function, we can get a function of features in which we feed features.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that the machine is using.",
                "So, you can train this data, and the model of your model, which will tell you the new features, how many of them are priced.",
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we will assume that our data is represented in one function.",
                "We can get features in which we feed features."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "As a function, we can get a function of features in _____  we feed features.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "features"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, _____  are data that the machine is using.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "which",
                    "learning",
                    "features"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, you can train this _____ , and the model of your model, which will tell you the new features, how many of them are priced.",
                  "options": [
                    "features",
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Today Library",
              "key_points": [
                "today",
                "library",
                "good",
                "tell",
                "computer"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "I will tell you that today's topic is good computer.",
                "And the good computers that were used today were the average in the age of the age of the age.",
                "So, the high computer that was used today was very expensive.",
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am going to tell you that in today's video, gpus, cpus, cpus, i am going to be going to be going to be a technology.",
                "And they are going to use their library as a popular library."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "I will tell you that today's topic is _____  computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "good",
                    "tell",
                    "today"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good computers that were used _____  were the average in the age of the age of the age.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "library",
                    "tell",
                    "today"
                  ],
                  "answer": "today"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high _____  that was used today was very expensive.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "library",
                    "computer",
                    "tell"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "will",
                "talk",
                "salary"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that the machine is using.",
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we will assume that our data is represented in one function.",
                "If you are doing this in deep learning, you will be able to do this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what _____  learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "talk",
                    "learning",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "talk",
                    "salary",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that the machine is using.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "deep",
                    "salary",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "2580c593-96e0-4317-a948-4e9c8b27b882": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "[enforce fail at alloc_cpu.cpp:121] data. DefaultCPUAllocator: not enough memory: you tried to allocate 5822933016 bytes."
  },
  "27d817a4-283a-498f-9a60-32bc9916b55b": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "Transcript not available. Whisper is disabled."
  },
  "c2268247-b2dd-4547-8130-f5141778863e": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": []
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "0833914e-49b5-4357-a09b-1db708021fee": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": []
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "9dedb8e4-f660-442f-96ee-45f8c9bb02a0": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": []
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "4b70e8c9-80fb-4f42-9133-d34ff6807cc3": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": []
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "3307878f-df30-489f-9bfd-05142e35a8ba": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "9f844569-ded0-4742-84d7-3b993db50f09": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "53599302-4cdf-4196-919f-d475e19cddaf": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "9e78416f-efe2-4301-8e84-0a27d84c0b02": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "61237336-31d1-4b60-8930-e06087c34164": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep _____  about this.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "will",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "many",
                    "learning",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "talk",
                    "learning",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "talk",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a _____ , represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle _____  which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "I will tell you that today's topic is good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "cpus",
                    "computer",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "popular",
                    "cpus",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "I will tell you that today's topic is good _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "cpus",
                    "popular",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "experiment",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "experiment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "experiment",
                    "will",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "8132ad10-421c-460a-ad49-75eb952e0b15": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what _____  learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "deep",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "will",
                    "video",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about _____  science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "many",
                    "data",
                    "talk",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "brain",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "many",
                    "brain",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our _____  is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "which",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "weights",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "I will tell you that today's topic is good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good _____ s that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "computer",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "I will tell you that today's topic is good _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "level",
                    "experiment",
                    "learn",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "talk",
                    "learn",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "level",
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "b638a9f8-2783-470a-8033-99ba51c1a287": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the deep _____  job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "will",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep _____  about this.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "will",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "data",
                    "talk",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "data",
                    "talk",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a _____ , represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "learning",
                    "function",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function _____  represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "weights",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, _____  are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "I will tell you that today's topic is good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "gpus",
                    "cpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good _____ s that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "good",
                    "popular",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "I will tell you that today's topic is good _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "talk",
                    "will",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "experiment",
                    "will",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "level",
                    "learn",
                    "experiment",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "32880ef4-496e-4455-91f4-5481bf647ebb": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Klearning (Advanced)",
      "difficulty": "advanced",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep klearning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this _____ , i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "video"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about _____  science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "video",
                    "will",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "many",
                    "brain",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "brain",
                    "learning",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "data",
                    "brain",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about _____  algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle _____  which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "I will tell you that today's topic is good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "popular",
                    "good",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "gpus",
                    "good",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "I will tell you that today's topic is _____  computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "level",
                    "will",
                    "experiment",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "level",
                    "talk",
                    "learn",
                    "experiment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "ad41ee3e-c9af-4adf-baf7-db9565f9ae11": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the deep _____  job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about _____  science, but many people have also been deep learning about this.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "You guys have heard about ai that you have heard about data science, but many people have also been deep learning about this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "brain",
                    "many",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "many",
                    "learning",
                    "talk",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "talk",
                    "many",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about _____  algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "weights",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function _____  represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "I will tell you that today's topic is good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "popular",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good _____ s that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "popular",
                    "computer",
                    "good",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "I will tell you that today's topic is good _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "popular",
                    "computer",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "learn",
                    "talk",
                    "experiment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "43abc68d-7df4-48a6-91e7-28e847e2f519": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what _____  learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about _____  learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "deep",
                    "video",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of _____  in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "many",
                    "learning",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "many",
                    "brain",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "talk",
                    "learning",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our _____  is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "data",
                    "weights",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "popular",
                    "computer",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good _____ s that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high _____  that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "popular",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "learn",
                    "talk",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "talk",
                    "experiment",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "c03e9dab-0bb0-4ee2-bd28-6124478af3f0": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deepleaning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deepleaning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what _____  learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the deep _____  job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "deep",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "talk",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "many",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "data",
                    "brain",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a _____ , represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "weights",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function _____  represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "weights",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and _____ , i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "popular",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "gpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "experiment",
                    "learn",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "talk",
                    "will",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "will",
                    "level",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "2b95cc67-f815-41c7-940f-0ad1ad7a6c9e": {
    "status": "processing",
    "result": null,
    "error": null
  },
  "089f8ee9-102c-45a4-baf1-ac64dc1a4a2e": {
    "status": "processing",
    "result": null,
    "error": null
  },
  "5558adc3-8839-4fc7-a5f6-1d99170f7170": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about _____  learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "brain",
                    "talk",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "brain",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "brain",
                    "many",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a _____ , represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "weights",
                    "learning",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and _____ , i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "popular",
                    "gpus",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "gpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "cpus",
                    "good",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "learn",
                    "level",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "learn",
                    "level",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "level",
                    "will",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "359ebaba-214c-4863-817c-c440768c325e": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: introduction to deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "video",
                    "deep",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "deep",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "many",
                    "brain",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "talk",
                    "learning",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "brain",
                    "learning",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a _____ , represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our _____ , we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "weights",
                    "function",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "weights"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "popular",
                    "gpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "popular",
                    "computer",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "popular",
                    "computer",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "talk",
                    "learn",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "experiment",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "experiment",
                    "will",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 2: basics of deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about _____  learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of _____  in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our _____  is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle _____  which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and _____ , i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "popular",
                    "cpus",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "gpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "gpus",
                    "cpus",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high _____  that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "gpus",
                    "good",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "learn",
                    "experiment",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "talk",
                    "experiment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "experiment",
                    "learn",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 3: intermediate deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VyWAvY2CF9c",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Data Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "data",
                "deep",
                "machine",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Deep learning is a subset machine learning which in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of learning which are machine learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                "To put it simply, deep learning is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                "These new red box contain a number of hidden layers through which data is processed, allowing for the machine to go deep in its learning, making connections and weighing input for the best results.",
                "Only when the data is too big which happens all the time in machine learning and when we can't pass all the data to the computer once."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Deep _____  is a subset machine learning which in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "learning",
                    "deep",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of _____  which are machine learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "which",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To put it simply, deep _____  is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Model Network Loss",
              "key_points": [
                "model",
                "network",
                "loss",
                "data",
                "function"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "They're tied to get the loss function and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                "If we use linear activation functions to model a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model.",
                "But essentially once our data has been fed forward propagation occurs and the losses compared against the loss function and the parameters are adjusted based on the loss incurred."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "They're tied to get the loss function and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the _____  in response to the output of the loss function.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "loss",
                    "function",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we use linear activation functions to _____  a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "network",
                    "loss",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training _____  with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "loss",
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Network Neural Layer",
              "key_points": [
                "network",
                "neural",
                "layer",
                "neurons",
                "output"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like a fully connected neural network, a cnn is composed of an input layer and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                "Isn't the output layer supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the neural network to the expected output.",
                "A convolutional neural network or cnn for short is a type of deep neural network architecture designed for specific tasks like image classification.",
                "When we put all these techniques together, we get an architect, a deeper neural network, quite different from a fully connected neural network."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like a fully connected neural _____ , a cnn is composed of an input layer and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                  "options": [
                    "neurons",
                    "layer",
                    "network",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Isn't the _____  layer supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                  "options": [
                    "output",
                    "neural",
                    "network",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the _____  network to the expected output.",
                  "options": [
                    "neurons",
                    "neural",
                    "layer",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Function Activation Functions",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "activation",
                "functions",
                "linear",
                "value"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a value closed slope of the line.",
                "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the activation function of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                "Remember a combination of linear functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                "An advantage of this activation function is that unlike the linear function, the output of this function is going to be in the range 0 to 1, inclusive.",
                "The red defined linear unit or the value function is defined as afx equal to the max from 0 to x. at first up, this would look like a linear function, ?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the _____  is proportional to the input by a value closed slope of the line.",
                  "options": [
                    "value",
                    "functions",
                    "activation",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "activation"
                },
                {
                  "question": "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are _____  in nature, the activation function of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                  "options": [
                    "functions",
                    "function",
                    "linear",
                    "value"
                  ],
                  "answer": "linear"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Remember a combination of _____  functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                  "options": [
                    "activation",
                    "function",
                    "functions",
                    "linear"
                  ],
                  "answer": "linear"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Data Model Training",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "model",
                "training",
                "will",
                "validation"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "After training, it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training data but not on testing data.",
                "This means we can obtain a model with better validation set error and thus hopefully better test set error by stopping training at the point where the error and the validation set starts to increase.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "After _____ , it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                  "options": [
                    "training",
                    "validation",
                    "data",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "training"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the _____  will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "validation",
                    "will",
                    "model",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "One of the most common challenges you'll face from _____  models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training data but not on testing data.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "will",
                    "training",
                    "validation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "training"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 4: advanced deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VyWAvY2CF9c",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Data Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "data",
                "deep",
                "machine",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Deep learning is a subset machine learning which in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of learning which are machine learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                "To put it simply, deep learning is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                "These new red box contain a number of hidden layers through which data is processed, allowing for the machine to go deep in its learning, making connections and weighing input for the best results.",
                "Only when the data is too big which happens all the time in machine learning and when we can't pass all the data to the computer once."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Deep learning is a subset machine learning _____  in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of learning which are machine learning concepts but i extended the _____  learning as well.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To put it simply, _____  learning is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "deep",
                    "which",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Model Network Loss",
              "key_points": [
                "model",
                "network",
                "loss",
                "data",
                "function"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "They're tied to get the loss function and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                "If we use linear activation functions to model a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model.",
                "But essentially once our data has been fed forward propagation occurs and the losses compared against the loss function and the parameters are adjusted based on the loss incurred."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "They're tied to get the loss function and _____  parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                  "options": [
                    "network",
                    "function",
                    "loss",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we use linear activation functions to model a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and _____  hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "data",
                    "function",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "loss",
                    "network",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Network Neural Layer",
              "key_points": [
                "network",
                "neural",
                "layer",
                "neurons",
                "output"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like a fully connected neural network, a cnn is composed of an input layer and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                "Isn't the output layer supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the neural network to the expected output.",
                "A convolutional neural network or cnn for short is a type of deep neural network architecture designed for specific tasks like image classification.",
                "When we put all these techniques together, we get an architect, a deeper neural network, quite different from a fully connected neural network."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like a fully connected neural network, a cnn is composed of an input layer and _____  layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "neurons",
                    "network",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Isn't the _____  layer supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                  "options": [
                    "neurons",
                    "network",
                    "output",
                    "neural"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted _____  by the neural network to the expected output.",
                  "options": [
                    "neurons",
                    "layer",
                    "neural",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Function Activation Functions",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "activation",
                "functions",
                "linear",
                "value"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a value closed slope of the line.",
                "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the activation function of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                "Remember a combination of linear functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                "An advantage of this activation function is that unlike the linear function, the output of this function is going to be in the range 0 to 1, inclusive.",
                "The red defined linear unit or the value function is defined as afx equal to the max from 0 to x. at first up, this would look like a linear function, ?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Maybe you will thought about a _____  function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a value closed slope of the line.",
                  "options": [
                    "value",
                    "activation",
                    "linear",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "linear"
                },
                {
                  "question": "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the activation _____  of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                  "options": [
                    "linear",
                    "activation",
                    "functions",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Remember a combination of _____  functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "linear",
                    "activation",
                    "value"
                  ],
                  "answer": "linear"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Data Model Training",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "model",
                "training",
                "will",
                "validation"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "After training, it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training data but not on testing data.",
                "This means we can obtain a model with better validation set error and thus hopefully better test set error by stopping training at the point where the error and the validation set starts to increase.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "After _____ , it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                  "options": [
                    "training",
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "validation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "training"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training _____  with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "training",
                    "will",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training _____ s is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training data but not on testing data.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "training",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 5: deep learning projects",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MFSFcPsMsuE",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Projects Even Will",
              "key_points": [
                "projects",
                "even",
                "will",
                "step",
                "example"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Today i'm sharing four example aiml projects that would impress me if i was reviewing your resume to join my team at amazon.",
                "My goal is to inspire you to build genuinely cool, possibly even useful projects that you're excited about, and help get you where you want in your career.",
                "Before we get into the example projects, let me lay out how i approach project planning.",
                "This will hopefully clear up a lot of the overwhelming and mysteriousness that new folks have when trying to come up with real projects."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Today i'm sharing four _____  aiml projects that would impress me if i was reviewing your resume to join my team at amazon.",
                  "options": [
                    "example",
                    "even",
                    "projects",
                    "step"
                  ],
                  "answer": "example"
                },
                {
                  "question": "My goal is to inspire you to build genuinely cool, possibly even useful _____  that you're excited about, and help get you where you want in your career.",
                  "options": [
                    "example",
                    "projects",
                    "will",
                    "even"
                  ],
                  "answer": "projects"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Before we get into the example _____ , let me lay out how i approach project planning.",
                  "options": [
                    "step",
                    "even",
                    "example",
                    "projects"
                  ],
                  "answer": "projects"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Data Model Training",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "model",
                "training",
                "will",
                "what"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "First, what data will you need and how will you get it?",
                "The training data gets pre-processed through a pipeline that handles data ingestion, data validation with deep checks, and feeds into a convolutional neural network, but with tensorflow.",
                "But in the real world, you need data pipelines, automated training, model validation, deployment, automation, monitoring, feedback loops, all kinds of stuff.",
                "For data and training, i used a mix of free data sets i found online."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "First, _____  data will you need and how will you get it?",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "model",
                    "what"
                  ],
                  "answer": "what"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The _____  data gets pre-processed through a pipeline that handles data ingestion, data validation with deep checks, and feeds into a convolutional neural network, but with tensorflow.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "training",
                    "what",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "training"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But in the real world, you need _____  pipelines, automated training, model validation, deployment, automation, monitoring, feedback loops, all kinds of stuff.",
                  "options": [
                    "training",
                    "data",
                    "what",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Simple Some Book",
              "key_points": [
                "simple",
                "some",
                "book",
                "preferences",
                "recommendations"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Take a picture of the book shelf with your phone and an ai model recognizes the books and makes recommendations.",
                "For data collection and storage, i needed some way to store user reading history and preferences, so i used a postgres database.",
                "Then i used gpt40 again to generate personalized recommendations based on the user's preferences and reading history.",
                "Lastly, i built in monitoring and alerting with a simple admin dashboard, added some comprehensive tests, and i did my best to follow security best practices.",
                "The ui would be super simple, which is a camera button, step of photo, get a prediction, maybe with some confidence interval."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Take a picture of the book shelf with your phone and an ai model recognizes the books and makes _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "simple",
                    "recommendations",
                    "preferences",
                    "some"
                  ],
                  "answer": "recommendations"
                },
                {
                  "question": "For data collection and storage, i needed _____  way to store user reading history and preferences, so i used a postgres database.",
                  "options": [
                    "recommendations",
                    "book",
                    "preferences",
                    "some"
                  ],
                  "answer": "some"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i used gpt40 again to generate personalized _____  based on the user's preferences and reading history.",
                  "options": [
                    "recommendations",
                    "preferences",
                    "some",
                    "simple"
                  ],
                  "answer": "recommendations"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Model Machine",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "model",
                "machine",
                "project",
                "added"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So if you want something a little bit easier, and a little bit more machine learning focused, the next project is for you.",
                "Most people learning machine learning build models in jupyter notebooks, maybe save them in pickle files in call it a day.",
                "This project demonstrates who understand production machine learning engineering, not just building models.",
                "It demonstrates core machine learning engineering skills because it shows you understand the full ai product lifecycle, all the way from data ingestion to deployment."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So if you want something a little bit easier, and a little bit more _____  learning focused, the next project is for you.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "added",
                    "machine",
                    "project"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Most people _____  machine learning build models in jupyter notebooks, maybe save them in pickle files in call it a day.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "model",
                    "project",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "This project demonstrates who understand production _____  learning engineering, not just building models.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "learning",
                    "machine",
                    "project"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Project Work Time",
              "key_points": [
                "project",
                "work",
                "time",
                "they",
                "more"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The next project is a bit more ambitious, but first, one thing that comes up a lot when talking about building portfolio projects is how to have time to work on them.",
                "Everyone had different ideas about where to go, different budgets, different dates they're available, places they've already been, places they don't want to go, what vibe they want.",
                "The stats feature shows me how much time i'm spending on each project, which can help give some visibility into where your time sinks are, or what you've been neglecting.",
                "Now on to the next project, which did take a couple weeks of my side project time.",
                "They're all projects iv, they're built personally, or were designed by one of my mentees."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The next project is a bit _____  ambitious, but first, one thing that comes up a lot when talking about building portfolio projects is how to have time to work on them.",
                  "options": [
                    "work",
                    "time",
                    "they",
                    "more"
                  ],
                  "answer": "more"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Everyone had different ideas about where to go, different budgets, different dates _____ 're available, places they've already been, places they don't want to go, what vibe they want.",
                  "options": [
                    "time",
                    "they",
                    "more",
                    "project"
                  ],
                  "answer": "they"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The stats feature shows me how much _____  i'm spending on each project, which can help give some visibility into where your time sinks are, or what you've been neglecting.",
                  "options": [
                    "project",
                    "time",
                    "work",
                    "more"
                  ],
                  "answer": "time"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "1ee5fb34-6955-42b6-968c-89b1063546a2": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: introduction to deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what deep _____  is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "deep",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about _____  learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "will",
                    "deep",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "many",
                    "data",
                    "brain",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "brain",
                    "data",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "talk",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a _____ , represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "weights",
                    "learning",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle _____  which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "which",
                    "weights",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are _____  that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "computer",
                    "good",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good _____ s that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "popular",
                    "gpus",
                    "computer",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high _____  that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "cpus",
                    "computer",
                    "good"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "experiment",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "experiment",
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "talk",
                    "experiment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 2: basics of deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this _____ , i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "video"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the deep _____  job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "many",
                    "brain",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "brain",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "brain",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about _____  algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "which",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle _____  which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, _____  are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "computer",
                    "good",
                    "cpus",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the good _____ s that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "cpus",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "computer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "gpus",
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "popular"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "learn",
                    "will",
                    "talk",
                    "level"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "experiment",
                    "learn",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "level",
                    "experiment",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 3: intermediate deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VyWAvY2CF9c",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Data Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "data",
                "deep",
                "machine",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Deep learning is a subset machine learning which in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of learning which are machine learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                "To put it simply, deep learning is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                "These new red box contain a number of hidden layers through which data is processed, allowing for the machine to go deep in its learning, making connections and weighing input for the best results.",
                "Only when the data is too big which happens all the time in machine learning and when we can't pass all the data to the computer once."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Deep learning is a subset machine learning _____  in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "which",
                    "machine",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of learning which are _____  learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "deep",
                    "learning",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To put it simply, deep learning is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from _____  by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Model Network Loss",
              "key_points": [
                "model",
                "network",
                "loss",
                "data",
                "function"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "They're tied to get the loss function and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                "If we use linear activation functions to model a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model.",
                "But essentially once our data has been fed forward propagation occurs and the losses compared against the loss function and the parameters are adjusted based on the loss incurred."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "They're tied to get the loss _____  and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "model",
                    "loss",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we use linear activation functions to _____  a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "loss",
                    "network",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training _____  with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "data",
                    "model",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Network Neural Layer",
              "key_points": [
                "network",
                "neural",
                "layer",
                "neurons",
                "output"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like a fully connected neural network, a cnn is composed of an input layer and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                "Isn't the output layer supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the neural network to the expected output.",
                "A convolutional neural network or cnn for short is a type of deep neural network architecture designed for specific tasks like image classification.",
                "When we put all these techniques together, we get an architect, a deeper neural network, quite different from a fully connected neural network."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like a fully connected neural _____ , a cnn is composed of an input layer and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "neural",
                    "neurons",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Isn't the output _____  supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "output",
                    "neural",
                    "neurons"
                  ],
                  "answer": "layer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the neural _____  to the expected output.",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "network",
                    "neurons",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Function Activation Functions",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "activation",
                "functions",
                "linear",
                "value"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a value closed slope of the line.",
                "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the activation function of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                "Remember a combination of linear functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                "An advantage of this activation function is that unlike the linear function, the output of this function is going to be in the range 0 to 1, inclusive.",
                "The red defined linear unit or the value function is defined as afx equal to the max from 0 to x. at first up, this would look like a linear function, ?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a _____  closed slope of the line.",
                  "options": [
                    "value",
                    "linear",
                    "activation",
                    "functions"
                  ],
                  "answer": "value"
                },
                {
                  "question": "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the activation _____  of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                  "options": [
                    "functions",
                    "linear",
                    "function",
                    "activation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Remember a combination of linear _____  in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                  "options": [
                    "functions",
                    "value",
                    "linear",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "functions"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Data Model Training",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "model",
                "training",
                "will",
                "validation"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "After training, it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training data but not on testing data.",
                "This means we can obtain a model with better validation set error and thus hopefully better test set error by stopping training at the point where the error and the validation set starts to increase.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "After training, it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "validation",
                    "training",
                    "data",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training _____  with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "validation",
                    "data",
                    "training",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training _____  but not on testing data.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "model",
                    "validation",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 4: advanced deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VyWAvY2CF9c",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Data Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "data",
                "deep",
                "machine",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Deep learning is a subset machine learning which in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from data.",
                "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of learning which are machine learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                "To put it simply, deep learning is a machine learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                "These new red box contain a number of hidden layers through which data is processed, allowing for the machine to go deep in its learning, making connections and weighing input for the best results.",
                "Only when the data is too big which happens all the time in machine learning and when we can't pass all the data to the computer once."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Deep learning is a subset machine learning which in turn is a subset of artificial intelligence, which involves more traditional methods to learn representations directly from _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "deep",
                    "data",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this section, we're going to talk about the different types of _____  which are machine learning concepts but i extended the deep learning as well.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "learning",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To put it simply, deep learning is a _____  learning technique that learns features and tasks directly from data by running inputs through a biologically inspired new network architecture.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "machine",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Model Network Loss",
              "key_points": [
                "model",
                "network",
                "loss",
                "data",
                "function"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "They're tied to get the loss function and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                "If we use linear activation functions to model a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model.",
                "But essentially once our data has been fed forward propagation occurs and the losses compared against the loss function and the parameters are adjusted based on the loss incurred."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "They're tied to get the _____  function and model parameters of the weights and biases by updating the network in response to the output of the loss function.",
                  "options": [
                    "loss",
                    "function",
                    "network",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we use linear activation functions to _____  a data, the no matter how many hidden layers and network hands, it will always become equivalent to having a single layer network.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "data",
                    "loss",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the _____  will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "data",
                    "model",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Network Neural Layer",
              "key_points": [
                "network",
                "neural",
                "layer",
                "neurons",
                "output"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like a fully connected neural network, a cnn is composed of an input layer and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                "Isn't the output layer supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the neural network to the expected output.",
                "A convolutional neural network or cnn for short is a type of deep neural network architecture designed for specific tasks like image classification.",
                "When we put all these techniques together, we get an architect, a deeper neural network, quite different from a fully connected neural network."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like a fully connected neural network, a cnn is composed of an input _____  and output layer and several hidden layers between the two.",
                  "options": [
                    "output",
                    "neural",
                    "network",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "layer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Isn't the output _____  supposed to be the final layer where we get the final output?",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "network",
                    "neurons",
                    "neural"
                  ],
                  "answer": "layer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Really simply, a loss function is a way to quantify the deviation of the predicted output by the _____  network to the expected output.",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "network",
                    "neural",
                    "neurons"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Function Activation Functions",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "activation",
                "functions",
                "linear",
                "value"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a value closed slope of the line.",
                "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the activation function of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                "Remember a combination of linear functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                "An advantage of this activation function is that unlike the linear function, the output of this function is going to be in the range 0 to 1, inclusive.",
                "The red defined linear unit or the value function is defined as afx equal to the max from 0 to x. at first up, this would look like a linear function, ?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Maybe you will thought about a linear function, a straight line function where the activation is proportional to the input by a _____  closed slope of the line.",
                  "options": [
                    "linear",
                    "functions",
                    "value",
                    "activation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "value"
                },
                {
                  "question": "No matter how many layers you have, if all of them are linear in nature, the _____  function of the final layer is nothing but just a linear function of the input of the first layer.",
                  "options": [
                    "linear",
                    "functions",
                    "function",
                    "activation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "activation"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Remember a combination of _____  functions in the linear manner is still another linear function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "activation",
                    "linear",
                    "functions"
                  ],
                  "answer": "linear"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Data Model Training",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "model",
                "training",
                "will",
                "validation"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "After training, it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the model will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training data but not on testing data.",
                "This means we can obtain a model with better validation set error and thus hopefully better test set error by stopping training at the point where the error and the validation set starts to increase.",
                "They have this abstract concept of sequential memory and because of this, we are able to model certain areas of data, sequential data that stand alone neural networks aren't able to model."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "After _____ , it will take a new unseen inputs and will determine which label the new inputs will be classified as based on prior training data.",
                  "options": [
                    "training",
                    "model",
                    "data",
                    "validation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "training"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The algorithm will be given training data with emails that are both spam and not spam and the _____  will find the features within the data that call later either class and create mapping function.",
                  "options": [
                    "validation",
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "One of the most common challenges you'll face from training models is a problem of overfitting, a situation where your model performs exceptionally well on training _____  but not on testing data.",
                  "options": [
                    "validation",
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 5: deep learning projects",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MFSFcPsMsuE",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Projects Even Will",
              "key_points": [
                "projects",
                "even",
                "will",
                "step",
                "example"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Today i'm sharing four example aiml projects that would impress me if i was reviewing your resume to join my team at amazon.",
                "My goal is to inspire you to build genuinely cool, possibly even useful projects that you're excited about, and help get you where you want in your career.",
                "Before we get into the example projects, let me lay out how i approach project planning.",
                "This will hopefully clear up a lot of the overwhelming and mysteriousness that new folks have when trying to come up with real projects."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Today i'm sharing four example aiml _____  that would impress me if i was reviewing your resume to join my team at amazon.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "example",
                    "step",
                    "projects"
                  ],
                  "answer": "projects"
                },
                {
                  "question": "My goal is to inspire you to build genuinely cool, possibly _____  useful projects that you're excited about, and help get you where you want in your career.",
                  "options": [
                    "even",
                    "projects",
                    "will",
                    "step"
                  ],
                  "answer": "even"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Before we get into the example _____ , let me lay out how i approach project planning.",
                  "options": [
                    "even",
                    "will",
                    "example",
                    "projects"
                  ],
                  "answer": "projects"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Data Model Training",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "model",
                "training",
                "will",
                "what"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "First, what data will you need and how will you get it?",
                "The training data gets pre-processed through a pipeline that handles data ingestion, data validation with deep checks, and feeds into a convolutional neural network, but with tensorflow.",
                "But in the real world, you need data pipelines, automated training, model validation, deployment, automation, monitoring, feedback loops, all kinds of stuff.",
                "For data and training, i used a mix of free data sets i found online."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "First, _____  data will you need and how will you get it?",
                  "options": [
                    "training",
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "what"
                  ],
                  "answer": "what"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The training _____  gets pre-processed through a pipeline that handles data ingestion, data validation with deep checks, and feeds into a convolutional neural network, but with tensorflow.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "training",
                    "will",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But in the real world, you need data pipelines, automated _____ , model validation, deployment, automation, monitoring, feedback loops, all kinds of stuff.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "what",
                    "model",
                    "training"
                  ],
                  "answer": "training"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Simple Some Book",
              "key_points": [
                "simple",
                "some",
                "book",
                "preferences",
                "recommendations"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Take a picture of the book shelf with your phone and an ai model recognizes the books and makes recommendations.",
                "For data collection and storage, i needed some way to store user reading history and preferences, so i used a postgres database.",
                "Then i used gpt40 again to generate personalized recommendations based on the user's preferences and reading history.",
                "Lastly, i built in monitoring and alerting with a simple admin dashboard, added some comprehensive tests, and i did my best to follow security best practices.",
                "The ui would be super simple, which is a camera button, step of photo, get a prediction, maybe with some confidence interval."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Take a picture of the _____  shelf with your phone and an ai model recognizes the books and makes recommendations.",
                  "options": [
                    "preferences",
                    "recommendations",
                    "simple",
                    "book"
                  ],
                  "answer": "book"
                },
                {
                  "question": "For data collection and storage, i needed some way to store user reading history and _____ , so i used a postgres database.",
                  "options": [
                    "preferences",
                    "some",
                    "recommendations",
                    "simple"
                  ],
                  "answer": "preferences"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i used gpt40 again to generate personalized _____  based on the user's preferences and reading history.",
                  "options": [
                    "book",
                    "preferences",
                    "simple",
                    "recommendations"
                  ],
                  "answer": "recommendations"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Model Machine",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "model",
                "machine",
                "project",
                "added"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So if you want something a little bit easier, and a little bit more machine learning focused, the next project is for you.",
                "Most people learning machine learning build models in jupyter notebooks, maybe save them in pickle files in call it a day.",
                "This project demonstrates who understand production machine learning engineering, not just building models.",
                "It demonstrates core machine learning engineering skills because it shows you understand the full ai product lifecycle, all the way from data ingestion to deployment."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So if you want something a little bit easier, and a little bit more machine learning focused, the next _____  is for you.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "project",
                    "added",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "project"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Most people _____  machine learning build models in jupyter notebooks, maybe save them in pickle files in call it a day.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "project",
                    "added",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "This project demonstrates who understand production _____  learning engineering, not just building models.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "machine",
                    "model",
                    "added"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Project Work Time",
              "key_points": [
                "project",
                "work",
                "time",
                "they",
                "more"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The next project is a bit more ambitious, but first, one thing that comes up a lot when talking about building portfolio projects is how to have time to work on them.",
                "Everyone had different ideas about where to go, different budgets, different dates they're available, places they've already been, places they don't want to go, what vibe they want.",
                "The stats feature shows me how much time i'm spending on each project, which can help give some visibility into where your time sinks are, or what you've been neglecting.",
                "Now on to the next project, which did take a couple weeks of my side project time.",
                "They're all projects iv, they're built personally, or were designed by one of my mentees."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The next _____  is a bit more ambitious, but first, one thing that comes up a lot when talking about building portfolio projects is how to have time to work on them.",
                  "options": [
                    "they",
                    "time",
                    "work",
                    "project"
                  ],
                  "answer": "project"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Everyone had different ideas about where to go, different budgets, different dates _____ 're available, places they've already been, places they don't want to go, what vibe they want.",
                  "options": [
                    "more",
                    "they",
                    "time",
                    "project"
                  ],
                  "answer": "they"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The stats feature shows me how much _____  i'm spending on each project, which can help give some visibility into where your time sinks are, or what you've been neglecting.",
                  "options": [
                    "more",
                    "project",
                    "time",
                    "work"
                  ],
                  "answer": "time"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "65cb1a97-5682-4038-99d9-4aa630677f16": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Machine Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: introduction to machine learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y4qO9unerGs",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Kathou Will Basic",
              "key_points": [
                "kathou",
                "will",
                "basic",
                "first",
                "fundamental"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Hello and welcome to soldiers who today's video arena comics and you may chompaitir whose basic kathou is the basic kathou is the best kathou in the world.",
                "And you will get the first time you are going to search for any product.",
                "Means that you have searched for your first time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                "2 number as a data dia and the condition kali we will see in the kali we will see in the third traditional programing system."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Hello and welcome to soldiers who today's video arena comics and you may chompaitir whose _____  kathou is the basic kathou is the best kathou in the world.",
                  "options": [
                    "fundamental",
                    "basic",
                    "kathou",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "basic"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And you will get the _____  time you are going to search for any product.",
                  "options": [
                    "first",
                    "kathou",
                    "fundamental",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "first"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Means that you have searched for your _____  time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                  "options": [
                    "fundamental",
                    "will",
                    "first",
                    "kathou"
                  ],
                  "answer": "first"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Sports Time Search",
              "key_points": [
                "sports",
                "time",
                "search",
                "product",
                "related"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Means that you have searched for your first time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                "All the product in your sports way related in your sports way related.",
                "Sift or sports related in your sports related.",
                "And you will get the first time you are going to search for any product.",
                "Then you can search for all the things you need to search for."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Means that you have searched for your first time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the _____ s in your product.",
                  "options": [
                    "product",
                    "search",
                    "time",
                    "sports"
                  ],
                  "answer": "product"
                },
                {
                  "question": "All the product in your sports way _____  in your sports way related.",
                  "options": [
                    "sports",
                    "time",
                    "related",
                    "product"
                  ],
                  "answer": "related"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Sift or sports _____  in your sports related.",
                  "options": [
                    "sports",
                    "search",
                    "time",
                    "related"
                  ],
                  "answer": "related"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Machine Data Program",
              "key_points": [
                "machine",
                "data",
                "program",
                "which",
                "what"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So how did the machine respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                "Program is data kizarwa thu ki is data mnqd kya jai ka according to the logic according to the code according to the program that we have written and free here we will get output generated.",
                "Which input dia for example program adhesion kali hai 2 number radiation.",
                "Which has given previous videos to toa brand and the machine.",
                "So, let us know what is the machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So how did the _____  respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "which",
                    "data",
                    "program"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Program is data kizarwa thu ki is data mnqd kya jai ka according to the logic according to the code according to the _____  that we have written and free here we will get output generated.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "program"
                  ],
                  "answer": "program"
                },
                {
                  "question": "_____  input dia for example program adhesion kali hai 2 number radiation.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "what",
                    "Which",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "Which"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Answer Question Trying",
              "key_points": [
                "answer",
                "question",
                "trying",
                "will",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "That if we have done the question, then this answer is the answer.",
                "If we have to learn this answer, then we will get the answer.",
                "The happens is the problem of a brain and brain is talking about a brain showing higher logic, there is another thing that we did at the time.",
                "2 number as a data dia and the condition kali we will see in the kali we will see in the third traditional programing system.",
                "So, the answer is the answer."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "That if we have done the question, then this _____  is the answer.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "answer",
                    "will",
                    "question"
                  ],
                  "answer": "answer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we have to learn this _____ , then we will get the answer.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "answer",
                    "will",
                    "question"
                  ],
                  "answer": "answer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The happens is the problem of a _____  and brain is talking about a brain showing higher logic, there is another thing that we did at the time.",
                  "options": [
                    "question",
                    "brain",
                    "trying",
                    "answer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "brain"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Video Machine Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "machine",
                "learning",
                "friends",
                "hierarchy"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So, friends, this is a basic video that i have mentioned about machine learning.",
                "So how did the machine respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                "A video like examples is made by machine learning.",
                "So, friends, if you like this video, like this video and very important.",
                "This is the way to make this machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So, friends, this is a basic _____  that i have mentioned about machine learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "friends",
                    "hierarchy",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "video"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So how did the _____  respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "friends",
                    "machine",
                    "hierarchy"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "A video like examples is made by _____  learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "hierarchy",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 2: machine learning fundamentals",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pj0neYUp9Tc",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Machine Learning World",
              "key_points": [
                "machine",
                "learning",
                "world",
                "machines",
                "they"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine learning and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong.",
                "In today's world, these machines or the robots are like they need to be programmed before they follow your instructions.",
                "Machine learning is the core of many futuristic technological advancement in our world.",
                "Deep learning is a subset of machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine _____  and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "they",
                    "learning",
                    "world"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In today's world, these machines or the robots are like _____  need to be programmed before they follow your instructions.",
                  "options": [
                    "world",
                    "machines",
                    "they",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "they"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Machine _____  is the core of many futuristic technological advancement in our world.",
                  "options": [
                    "world",
                    "machine",
                    "they",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Algorithm Supervised",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "algorithm",
                "supervised",
                "machine",
                "data"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Well, it is called as supervised learning because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                "New input data is introduced to the machine learning algorithm and it makes prediction based on the model.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "Now you might be wondering why this category of machine learning is named as supervised learning.",
                "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine learning and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Well, it is called as supervised _____  because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                  "options": [
                    "algorithm",
                    "supervised",
                    "data",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "New input data is introduced to the _____  learning algorithm and it makes prediction based on the model.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "data",
                    "machine",
                    "algorithm"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised _____ , unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "supervised",
                    "algorithm"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Sector Learning Model",
              "key_points": [
                "sector",
                "learning",
                "model",
                "next",
                "retail"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In banking sector reinforcement learning is used to create a next best offer model for a call centre.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "The result of supervised learning process is a predictive model, which is capable of associating a label duck or not duck to the new image presented to the model.",
                "Well, it is called as supervised learning because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                "Next comes the retail sector."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In banking sector reinforcement _____  is used to create a next best offer model for a call centre.",
                  "options": [
                    "next",
                    "retail",
                    "model",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised _____ , unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "sector",
                    "next",
                    "model",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The result of supervised learning process is a predictive _____ , which is capable of associating a label duck or not duck to the new image presented to the model.",
                  "options": [
                    "retail",
                    "model",
                    "learning",
                    "sector"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Machine Environment",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "machine",
                "environment",
                "agent",
                "reinforcement"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The reinforcement learning is about interaction between two elements, the environment and the learning agent.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "So let's discuss the third and the last type of machine learning that is reinforcement learning.",
                "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine learning and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong.",
                "Deep learning is a subset of machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The reinforcement _____  is about interaction between two elements, the environment and the learning agent.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "machine",
                    "environment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised _____ , unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "agent",
                    "learning",
                    "environment",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So let's discuss the third and the last type of machine _____  that is reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "learning",
                    "environment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Reinforcement Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "reinforcement",
                "learning",
                "bell",
                "food"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Even if the food was not given to him as the dog was reinforced that whenever the master will ring the bell he will get the food.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "Well, it is called as supervised learning because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                "So let's discuss the third and the last type of machine learning that is reinforcement learning.",
                "The reinforcement learning is about interaction between two elements, the environment and the learning agent."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Even if the _____  was not given to him as the dog was reinforced that whenever the master will ring the bell he will get the food.",
                  "options": [
                    "bell",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "learning",
                    "food"
                  ],
                  "answer": "food"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and _____  learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "food",
                    "bell",
                    "reinforcement"
                  ],
                  "answer": "reinforcement"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Well, it is called as supervised _____  because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                  "options": [
                    "bell",
                    "food",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 3: intermediate machine learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ORMx45xqWkA",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Deep Learning Library",
              "key_points": [
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "library",
                "tensors",
                "models"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The pytorch, an open-source deep learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of python.",
                "Pytorch has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                "Developers love prototyping with it, because it supports a dynamic computational graph, allowing models to be optimized at runtime."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The pytorch, an open-source _____  learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "tensors",
                    "models",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning _____  with just a few lines of python.",
                  "options": [
                    "library",
                    "deep",
                    "models",
                    "tensors"
                  ],
                  "answer": "models"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Pytorch has been used to train _____  for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                  "options": [
                    "models",
                    "tensors",
                    "learning",
                    "library"
                  ],
                  "answer": "models"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Pytorch Models Python",
              "key_points": [
                "pytorch",
                "models",
                "python",
                "tensor",
                "array"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like i mentioned, a tensor is similar to a multi-dimensional array, create a 2d array or matrix with python, then use torch to convert it into a tensor.",
                "Pytorch has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of python.",
                "The pytorch, an open-source deep learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                "Developers love prototyping with it, because it supports a dynamic computational graph, allowing models to be optimized at runtime."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like i mentioned, a tensor is similar to a multi-dimensional _____ , create a 2d array or matrix with python, then use torch to convert it into a tensor.",
                  "options": [
                    "models",
                    "python",
                    "pytorch",
                    "array"
                  ],
                  "answer": "array"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Pytorch has been used to train _____  for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                  "options": [
                    "tensor",
                    "python",
                    "models",
                    "array"
                  ],
                  "answer": "models"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "models",
                    "array",
                    "tensor",
                    "python"
                  ],
                  "answer": "python"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Build Neural Network",
              "key_points": [
                "build",
                "neural",
                "network",
                "image",
                "class"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "What you came here to do though is build a deep neural network, like an image classifier.",
                "To handle that, we can define a new class that inherits from the neural network module class.",
                "Congratulations, you just built a neural network.",
                "The pytorch, an open-source deep learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                "Pytorch has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "What you came here to do though is build a deep neural network, like an _____  classifier.",
                  "options": [
                    "class",
                    "build",
                    "image",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "image"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To handle that, we can define a new _____  that inherits from the neural network module class.",
                  "options": [
                    "build",
                    "image",
                    "network",
                    "class"
                  ],
                  "answer": "class"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Congratulations, you just built a neural _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "neural",
                    "build",
                    "network",
                    "class"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Data Layer Outputs",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "layer",
                "outputs",
                "output",
                "fully"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Linear is a fully connected layer that takes the flat and 28x28 image and transforms it to an output of 512. this layer is followed by a non-linear activation function.",
                "And finally, we finish with a fully connected layer that outputs the 10 labels the model is trying to predict.",
                "As each data point flows through it, it'll try to guess the output and gradually update a mapping of weights to determine the importance of a given variable.",
                "When activated, it means that feature might be important and outputs the node, otherwise it just outputs zero.",
                "Inside the constructor, we can build it out later by layer."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Linear is a fully connected layer that takes the flat and 28x28 image and transforms it to an _____  of 512. this layer is followed by a non-linear activation function.",
                  "options": [
                    "layer",
                    "output",
                    "outputs",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And finally, we finish with a fully connected layer that _____  the 10 labels the model is trying to predict.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "outputs",
                    "output",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "outputs"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As each data point flows through it, it'll try to guess the _____  and gradually update a mapping of weights to determine the importance of a given variable.",
                  "options": [
                    "outputs",
                    "layer",
                    "output",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Automatically Call",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "automatically",
                "call",
                "forward",
                "method"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "This will automatically call it forward method for training and prediction.",
                "With these pieces in place, the next step is to define a forward method that describes the flow of data.",
                "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of python.",
                "The flat and layer will take a multi-dimensional input, like an image, and convert it to one dimension.",
                "From there, sequential as you use, you create a container of layers that the data will flow through."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "This will automatically call it _____  method for training and prediction.",
                  "options": [
                    "method",
                    "call",
                    "will",
                    "forward"
                  ],
                  "answer": "forward"
                },
                {
                  "question": "With these pieces in place, the next step is to define a _____  method that describes the flow of data.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "call",
                    "method",
                    "forward"
                  ],
                  "answer": "forward"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "748a1073-ae48-4d73-8868-47952e0ca691": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Machine Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: introduction to machine learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y4qO9unerGs",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Kathou Will Basic",
              "key_points": [
                "kathou",
                "will",
                "basic",
                "first",
                "fundamental"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Hello and welcome to soldiers who today's video arena comics and you may chompaitir whose basic kathou is the basic kathou is the best kathou in the world.",
                "And you will get the first time you are going to search for any product.",
                "Means that you have searched for your first time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                "2 number as a data dia and the condition kali we will see in the kali we will see in the third traditional programing system."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Hello and welcome to soldiers who today's video arena comics and you may chompaitir whose basic _____  is the basic kathou is the best kathou in the world.",
                  "options": [
                    "fundamental",
                    "first",
                    "will",
                    "kathou"
                  ],
                  "answer": "kathou"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And you will get the _____  time you are going to search for any product.",
                  "options": [
                    "first",
                    "basic",
                    "kathou",
                    "fundamental"
                  ],
                  "answer": "first"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Means that you have searched for your _____  time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "first",
                    "fundamental",
                    "kathou"
                  ],
                  "answer": "first"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Sports Time Search",
              "key_points": [
                "sports",
                "time",
                "search",
                "product",
                "related"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Means that you have searched for your first time, or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                "All the product in your sports way related in your sports way related.",
                "Sift or sports related in your sports related.",
                "And you will get the first time you are going to search for any product.",
                "Then you can search for all the things you need to search for."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Means that you have searched for your first _____ , or for example, if you are searching for sports in your sports way, then after the second time, you will get all the products in your product.",
                  "options": [
                    "related",
                    "search",
                    "sports",
                    "time"
                  ],
                  "answer": "time"
                },
                {
                  "question": "All the product in your sports way _____  in your sports way related.",
                  "options": [
                    "sports",
                    "time",
                    "related",
                    "product"
                  ],
                  "answer": "related"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Sift or _____  related in your sports related.",
                  "options": [
                    "sports",
                    "time",
                    "related",
                    "product"
                  ],
                  "answer": "sports"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Machine Data Program",
              "key_points": [
                "machine",
                "data",
                "program",
                "which",
                "what"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So how did the machine respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                "Program is data kizarwa thu ki is data mnqd kya jai ka according to the logic according to the code according to the program that we have written and free here we will get output generated.",
                "Which input dia for example program adhesion kali hai 2 number radiation.",
                "Which has given previous videos to toa brand and the machine.",
                "So, let us know what is the machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So how did the _____  respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                  "options": [
                    "what",
                    "program",
                    "machine",
                    "which"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Program is _____  kizarwa thu ki is data mnqd kya jai ka according to the logic according to the code according to the program that we have written and free here we will get output generated.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "which",
                    "what",
                    "program"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which input dia for example _____  adhesion kali hai 2 number radiation.",
                  "options": [
                    "program",
                    "which",
                    "what",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "program"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Answer Question Trying",
              "key_points": [
                "answer",
                "question",
                "trying",
                "will",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "That if we have done the question, then this answer is the answer.",
                "If we have to learn this answer, then we will get the answer.",
                "The happens is the problem of a brain and brain is talking about a brain showing higher logic, there is another thing that we did at the time.",
                "2 number as a data dia and the condition kali we will see in the kali we will see in the third traditional programing system.",
                "So, the answer is the answer."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "That if we have done the question, then this _____  is the answer.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "question",
                    "trying",
                    "answer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "answer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we have to learn this _____ , then we will get the answer.",
                  "options": [
                    "trying",
                    "answer",
                    "question",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "answer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The happens is the problem of a _____  and brain is talking about a brain showing higher logic, there is another thing that we did at the time.",
                  "options": [
                    "question",
                    "answer",
                    "will",
                    "brain"
                  ],
                  "answer": "brain"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Video Machine Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "machine",
                "learning",
                "friends",
                "hierarchy"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So, friends, this is a basic video that i have mentioned about machine learning.",
                "So how did the machine respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                "A video like examples is made by machine learning.",
                "So, friends, if you like this video, like this video and very important.",
                "This is the way to make this machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So, friends, this is a basic video that i have mentioned about machine _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "hierarchy",
                    "friends",
                    "machine",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So how did the _____  respond to the machine, according to the machine, according to the program, and what did the output generate?",
                  "options": [
                    "friends",
                    "hierarchy",
                    "video",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "A video like examples is made by machine _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "hierarchy",
                    "friends"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 2: machine learning fundamentals",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pj0neYUp9Tc",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Machine Learning World",
              "key_points": [
                "machine",
                "learning",
                "world",
                "machines",
                "they"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine learning and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong.",
                "In today's world, these machines or the robots are like they need to be programmed before they follow your instructions.",
                "Machine learning is the core of many futuristic technological advancement in our world.",
                "Deep learning is a subset of machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine _____  and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong.",
                  "options": [
                    "world",
                    "machines",
                    "learning",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In today's world, these machines or the robots are like _____  need to be programmed before they follow your instructions.",
                  "options": [
                    "they",
                    "world",
                    "learning",
                    "machines"
                  ],
                  "answer": "they"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Machine _____  is the core of many futuristic technological advancement in our world.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "they",
                    "learning",
                    "machines"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Algorithm Supervised",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "algorithm",
                "supervised",
                "machine",
                "data"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Well, it is called as supervised learning because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                "New input data is introduced to the machine learning algorithm and it makes prediction based on the model.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "Now you might be wondering why this category of machine learning is named as supervised learning.",
                "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine learning and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Well, it is called as supervised _____  because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "learning",
                    "supervised",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "New input data is introduced to the _____  learning algorithm and it makes prediction based on the model.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "machine",
                    "algorithm",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "machine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised _____ , unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "data",
                    "algorithm",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Sector Learning Model",
              "key_points": [
                "sector",
                "learning",
                "model",
                "next",
                "retail"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In banking sector reinforcement learning is used to create a next best offer model for a call centre.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "The result of supervised learning process is a predictive model, which is capable of associating a label duck or not duck to the new image presented to the model.",
                "Well, it is called as supervised learning because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                "Next comes the retail sector."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In banking sector reinforcement learning is used to create a next best offer _____  for a call centre.",
                  "options": [
                    "retail",
                    "learning",
                    "model",
                    "next"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised _____ , unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "retail",
                    "learning",
                    "next"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The result of supervised _____  process is a predictive model, which is capable of associating a label duck or not duck to the new image presented to the model.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "learning",
                    "sector",
                    "next"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Machine Environment",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "machine",
                "environment",
                "agent",
                "reinforcement"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The reinforcement learning is about interaction between two elements, the environment and the learning agent.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "So let's discuss the third and the last type of machine learning that is reinforcement learning.",
                "They think that all the three of them, the ai, the machine learning and the deep learning, all the same, what they are wrong.",
                "Deep learning is a subset of machine learning."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The _____  learning is about interaction between two elements, the environment and the learning agent.",
                  "options": [
                    "agent",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "learning",
                    "machine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "reinforcement"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and _____  learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "machine",
                    "learning",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "agent"
                  ],
                  "answer": "reinforcement"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So let's discuss the third and the last type of machine _____  that is reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "environment",
                    "reinforcement",
                    "learning",
                    "agent"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Reinforcement Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "reinforcement",
                "learning",
                "bell",
                "food"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Even if the food was not given to him as the dog was reinforced that whenever the master will ring the bell he will get the food.",
                "The supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                "Well, it is called as supervised learning because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                "So let's discuss the third and the last type of machine learning that is reinforcement learning.",
                "The reinforcement learning is about interaction between two elements, the environment and the learning agent."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Even if the food was not given to him as the dog was reinforced that whenever the master will ring the _____  he will get the food.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "bell",
                    "learning",
                    "food"
                  ],
                  "answer": "bell"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The supervised _____ , unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning.",
                  "options": [
                    "food",
                    "will",
                    "learning",
                    "bell"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Well, it is called as supervised _____  because the process of an algorithm learning from the training dataset can be thought of as a teacher supervising the learning process.",
                  "options": [
                    "bell",
                    "will",
                    "food",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 3: intermediate machine learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ORMx45xqWkA",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Deep Learning Library",
              "key_points": [
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "library",
                "tensors",
                "models"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The pytorch, an open-source deep learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of python.",
                "Pytorch has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                "Developers love prototyping with it, because it supports a dynamic computational graph, allowing models to be optimized at runtime."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The pytorch, an open-source deep _____  framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                  "options": [
                    "library",
                    "models",
                    "learning",
                    "tensors"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning _____  with just a few lines of python.",
                  "options": [
                    "library",
                    "models",
                    "learning",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "models"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Pytorch has been used to train _____  for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "tensors",
                    "library",
                    "models"
                  ],
                  "answer": "models"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Pytorch Models Python",
              "key_points": [
                "pytorch",
                "models",
                "python",
                "tensor",
                "array"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like i mentioned, a tensor is similar to a multi-dimensional array, create a 2d array or matrix with python, then use torch to convert it into a tensor.",
                "Pytorch has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of python.",
                "The pytorch, an open-source deep learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                "Developers love prototyping with it, because it supports a dynamic computational graph, allowing models to be optimized at runtime."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like i mentioned, a _____  is similar to a multi-dimensional array, create a 2d array or matrix with python, then use torch to convert it into a tensor.",
                  "options": [
                    "array",
                    "pytorch",
                    "python",
                    "tensor"
                  ],
                  "answer": "tensor"
                },
                {
                  "question": "_____  has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few.",
                  "options": [
                    "Pytorch",
                    "tensor",
                    "python",
                    "array"
                  ],
                  "answer": "Pytorch"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "python",
                    "pytorch",
                    "array",
                    "models"
                  ],
                  "answer": "python"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Build Neural Network",
              "key_points": [
                "build",
                "neural",
                "network",
                "image",
                "class"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "What you came here to do though is build a deep neural network, like an image classifier.",
                "To handle that, we can define a new class that inherits from the neural network module class.",
                "Congratulations, you just built a neural network.",
                "The pytorch, an open-source deep learning framework, used to build some of the world's most famous artificial intelligence products.",
                "Pytorch has been used to train models for computer vision ai like tesla autopilot, image generators like stable diffusion, and speech recognition models like openai whisper, just to name a few."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "What you came here to do though is build a deep _____  network, like an image classifier.",
                  "options": [
                    "network",
                    "class",
                    "image",
                    "neural"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To handle that, we can define a new class that inherits from the neural _____  module class.",
                  "options": [
                    "image",
                    "class",
                    "build",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Congratulations, you just built a neural _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "network",
                    "class",
                    "image",
                    "build"
                  ],
                  "answer": "network"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Data Layer Outputs",
              "key_points": [
                "data",
                "layer",
                "outputs",
                "output",
                "fully"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Linear is a fully connected layer that takes the flat and 28x28 image and transforms it to an output of 512. this layer is followed by a non-linear activation function.",
                "And finally, we finish with a fully connected layer that outputs the 10 labels the model is trying to predict.",
                "As each data point flows through it, it'll try to guess the output and gradually update a mapping of weights to determine the importance of a given variable.",
                "When activated, it means that feature might be important and outputs the node, otherwise it just outputs zero.",
                "Inside the constructor, we can build it out later by layer."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Linear is a fully connected _____  that takes the flat and 28x28 image and transforms it to an output of 512. this layer is followed by a non-linear activation function.",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "output",
                    "fully",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "layer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And finally, we finish with a _____  connected layer that outputs the 10 labels the model is trying to predict.",
                  "options": [
                    "fully",
                    "layer",
                    "outputs",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "fully"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As each data point flows through it, it'll try to guess the _____  and gradually update a mapping of weights to determine the importance of a given variable.",
                  "options": [
                    "outputs",
                    "output",
                    "fully",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Automatically Call",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "automatically",
                "call",
                "forward",
                "method"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "This will automatically call it forward method for training and prediction.",
                "With these pieces in place, the next step is to define a forward method that describes the flow of data.",
                "Sounds complicated, but it's focused on usability will have you training machine learning models with just a few lines of python.",
                "The flat and layer will take a multi-dimensional input, like an image, and convert it to one dimension.",
                "From there, sequential as you use, you create a container of layers that the data will flow through."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "This will automatically call it forward _____  for training and prediction.",
                  "options": [
                    "method",
                    "forward",
                    "will",
                    "call"
                  ],
                  "answer": "method"
                },
                {
                  "question": "With these pieces in place, the next step is to define a forward _____  that describes the flow of data.",
                  "options": [
                    "automatically",
                    "method",
                    "forward",
                    "call"
                  ],
                  "answer": "method"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "bb3c43e6-789c-4f58-85a1-1f09c73a81bd": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Python (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: introduction to python",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr1f84rg4Nw",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Will List Post",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "list",
                "post",
                "print",
                "comment"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will post it on top of e if i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list which is pushing on top of all accounts.",
                "If i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list.",
                "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                "Or if we click on the list set, we will see that you will see the list on top of it.",
                "On my print, i will post it on top of the list."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will post it on top of e if i am going to post it on top of the _____ , i will post it on top of the list which is pushing on top of all accounts.",
                  "options": [
                    "list",
                    "will",
                    "print",
                    "comment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If i am going to post it on top of the _____ , i will post it on top of the list.",
                  "options": [
                    "comment",
                    "print",
                    "list",
                    "post"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to _____  it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                  "options": [
                    "post",
                    "print",
                    "list",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Will File Save",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "file",
                "save",
                "koluma",
                "harry"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And i will also get a koluma mode in koluma.",
                "Now, if i want to read a file, then i will get a ried mode in koluma.",
                "Similarly, if i am a type a, i will be a b. then i will show you."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And i will also get a _____  mode in koluma.",
                  "options": [
                    "file",
                    "will",
                    "koluma",
                    "harry"
                  ],
                  "answer": "koluma"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, if i want to read a file, then i will get a ried mode in _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "koluma",
                    "file",
                    "harry",
                    "save"
                  ],
                  "answer": "koluma"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Will Type Equal",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "type",
                "equal",
                "zero",
                "variable"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will show you that i am a type a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                "Like i am saying, if i am a type d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                "Similarly, if i am a type a, i will be a b. then i will show you.",
                "Now, if i get a friend content, then i will get a content that i will get in this variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you that i am a _____  a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "type",
                    "variable",
                    "zero"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to _____  in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                  "options": [
                    "zero",
                    "equal",
                    "type",
                    "variable"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Like i am saying, if i am a _____  d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "will",
                    "equal",
                    "variable"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "String Play Will",
              "key_points": [
                "string",
                "play",
                "will",
                "function",
                "print"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then you can play a string function.",
                "But if i am a print, i will be a print.",
                "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                "Then i will be a string variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then you can play a _____  function.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "function",
                    "will",
                    "string"
                  ],
                  "answer": "string"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But if i am a _____ , i will be a print.",
                  "options": [
                    "string",
                    "print",
                    "play",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to _____  it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "play",
                    "function",
                    "string"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "List Change Tuphine",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "change",
                "tuphine",
                "type",
                "video"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will show you that i am a type a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                "If i change my value to tuphine, i'll change my clothes to 2. if i'm going to have 22, i'll to carry on with me, to have these two colors.",
                "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                "Like i am saying, if i am a type d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                "This is the list from theinis list i have it was correct vayal limbs!!"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you that i am a _____  a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "tuphine",
                    "list",
                    "change"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If i change my value to _____ , i'll change my clothes to 2. if i'm going to have 22, i'll to carry on with me, to have these two colors.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "video",
                    "tuphine",
                    "change"
                  ],
                  "answer": "tuphine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to _____  in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                  "options": [
                    "tuphine",
                    "list",
                    "type",
                    "change"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 2: python fundamentals",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr1f84rg4Nw",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Will List Post",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "list",
                "post",
                "print",
                "comment"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will post it on top of e if i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list which is pushing on top of all accounts.",
                "If i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list.",
                "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                "Or if we click on the list set, we will see that you will see the list on top of it.",
                "On my print, i will post it on top of the list."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will _____  it on top of e if i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list which is pushing on top of all accounts.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "list",
                    "print",
                    "post"
                  ],
                  "answer": "post"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If i am going to _____  it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list.",
                  "options": [
                    "comment",
                    "print",
                    "will",
                    "post"
                  ],
                  "answer": "post"
                },
                {
                  "question": "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "post",
                    "will",
                    "comment",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Will File Save",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "file",
                "save",
                "koluma",
                "harry"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And i will also get a koluma mode in koluma.",
                "Now, if i want to read a file, then i will get a ried mode in koluma.",
                "Similarly, if i am a type a, i will be a b. then i will show you."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And i will also get a _____  mode in koluma.",
                  "options": [
                    "koluma",
                    "will",
                    "file",
                    "save"
                  ],
                  "answer": "koluma"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, if i want to read a _____ , then i will get a ried mode in koluma.",
                  "options": [
                    "koluma",
                    "will",
                    "save",
                    "file"
                  ],
                  "answer": "file"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Will Type Equal",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "type",
                "equal",
                "zero",
                "variable"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will show you that i am a type a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                "Like i am saying, if i am a type d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                "Similarly, if i am a type a, i will be a b. then i will show you.",
                "Now, if i get a friend content, then i will get a content that i will get in this variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you that i am a _____  a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                  "options": [
                    "equal",
                    "type",
                    "zero",
                    "variable"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to _____  in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                  "options": [
                    "variable",
                    "will",
                    "zero",
                    "type"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Like i am saying, if i am a _____  d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "zero",
                    "type",
                    "equal"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "String Play Will",
              "key_points": [
                "string",
                "play",
                "will",
                "function",
                "print"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then you can play a string function.",
                "But if i am a print, i will be a print.",
                "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                "Then i will be a string variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then you can _____  a string function.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "string",
                    "will",
                    "play"
                  ],
                  "answer": "play"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But if i am a _____ , i will be a print.",
                  "options": [
                    "string",
                    "will",
                    "print",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to _____  it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "function",
                    "play",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "List Change Tuphine",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "change",
                "tuphine",
                "type",
                "video"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will show you that i am a type a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                "If i change my value to tuphine, i'll change my clothes to 2. if i'm going to have 22, i'll to carry on with me, to have these two colors.",
                "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                "Like i am saying, if i am a type d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                "This is the list from theinis list i have it was correct vayal limbs!!"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you that i am a _____  a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                  "options": [
                    "tuphine",
                    "change",
                    "list",
                    "type"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If i change my value to _____ , i'll change my clothes to 2. if i'm going to have 22, i'll to carry on with me, to have these two colors.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "tuphine",
                    "list",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "tuphine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to _____  in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "list",
                    "change",
                    "type"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 3: intermediate python",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HGOBQPFzWKo",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Tuple Elements Inside",
              "key_points": [
                "tuple",
                "elements",
                "inside",
                "list",
                "element"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And now if we print my list and print the second list, then we see that the new list got created where each element is squared.",
                "And first of all, if we want to get the number of elements inside our tuple, we can just use the length method to length of my tuple.",
                "If we want to count some elements inside our tuple, so we can use my tuple dot count.",
                "So if i say my list equals and then i use the list function and put the tuple here, then i get a list out of it."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And now if we print my _____  and print the second list, then we see that the new list got created where each element is squared.",
                  "options": [
                    "tuple",
                    "elements",
                    "inside",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And first of all, if we want to get the number of elements inside our _____ , we can just use the length method to length of my tuple.",
                  "options": [
                    "elements",
                    "inside",
                    "tuple",
                    "element"
                  ],
                  "answer": "tuple"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If we want to count some _____  inside our tuple, so we can use my tuple dot count.",
                  "options": [
                    "element",
                    "tuple",
                    "elements",
                    "inside"
                  ],
                  "answer": "elements"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "List Inside Want",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "inside",
                "want",
                "method",
                "print"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And now if we print my list and print the second list, then we see that the new list got created where each element is squared.",
                "First of all, if you want to check how many elements do you have inside your list, you can do that with the length method.",
                "So if we assign this to a variable and print it, and we see that now we got our apple back and if we print our list, then we see that the apple is no longer in our list.",
                "And if you don't want to have this change, but rather create a new list, then you can do this, but with the build in sorted method, new list equals sorted.",
                "Now if you want to iterate over your list, you can do that simply with a four in loop, four, i in my list, colon, and then do something."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And now if we print my _____  and print the second list, then we see that the new list got created where each element is squared.",
                  "options": [
                    "list",
                    "print",
                    "method",
                    "inside"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "First of all, if you want to check how many elements do you have inside your _____ , you can do that with the length method.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "inside",
                    "list",
                    "method"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So if we assign this to a variable and _____  it, and we see that now we got our apple back and if we print our list, then we see that the apple is no longer in our list.",
                  "options": [
                    "want",
                    "method",
                    "inside",
                    "print"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "List Print Original",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "print",
                "original",
                "want",
                "create"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And then your original list and note that if you print your original list again, then you see this is still the same.",
                "So our example, if i append a lemon and if i print the copy and i also print the original, then we see that the original list now also has a lemon in it.",
                "And now if we print my list and print the second list, then we see that the new list got created where each element is squared.",
                "So if we assign this to a variable and print it, and we see that now we got our apple back and if we print our list, then we see that the apple is no longer in our list."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And then your original list and note that if you _____  your original list again, then you see this is still the same.",
                  "options": [
                    "original",
                    "print",
                    "create",
                    "want"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So our example, if i append a lemon and if i print the copy and i also print the _____ , then we see that the original list now also has a lemon in it.",
                  "options": [
                    "create",
                    "original",
                    "list",
                    "print"
                  ],
                  "answer": "original"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And now if we _____  my list and print the second list, then we see that the new list got created where each element is squared.",
                  "options": [
                    "want",
                    "print",
                    "create",
                    "original"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Index Item List",
              "key_points": [
                "index",
                "item",
                "list",
                "specify",
                "tuple"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And if you print this, and we see we have a new list that goes from index one to index five and the last item, the last index is excluded.",
                "So if we say item equals my tuple and then inside brackets, we specify the index that we want.",
                "So this is at index p. for example, if you say a, and we get index zero, if we want to get the index of l, then we get index three.",
                "So if i say my list equals and then i use the list function and put the tuple here, then i get a list out of it."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And if you print this, and we see we have a new list that goes from _____  one to index five and the last item, the last index is excluded.",
                  "options": [
                    "item",
                    "index",
                    "specify",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "index"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So if we say item equals my tuple and then inside brackets, we specify the _____  that we want.",
                  "options": [
                    "list",
                    "tuple",
                    "item",
                    "index"
                  ],
                  "answer": "index"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So this is at _____  p. for example, if you say a, and we get index zero, if we want to get the index of l, then we get index three.",
                  "options": [
                    "index",
                    "specify",
                    "tuple",
                    "list"
                  ],
                  "answer": "index"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Print Function",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "print",
                "function",
                "want",
                "equals"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So if you print the associated value for the name and we get max and if you want to look up the age, we get 28 and what will happen if we use a key that is not inside our dictionary.",
                "So if we run this then this statement is successful so it can print the name and if we want to access the last name then this statement will raise an exception a key error.",
                "What you rather want to do is you want to use the actual key so the key three is nine and then if you print the value then we see we get the nine.",
                "And then your item that you want to check, say banana, in my list, colon and say let's print.",
                "So if we assign this to a variable and print it, and we see that now we got our apple back and if we print our list, then we see that the apple is no longer in our list."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So if you _____  the associated value for the name and we get max and if you want to look up the age, we get 28 and what will happen if we use a key that is not inside our dictionary.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "want",
                    "function",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So if we run this then this statement is successful so it can _____  the name and if we want to access the last name then this statement will raise an exception a key error.",
                  "options": [
                    "equals",
                    "want",
                    "print",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What you rather want to do is you want to use the actual key so the key three is nine and then if you _____  the value then we see we get the nine.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "equals",
                    "will",
                    "want"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 4: advanced python",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr1f84rg4Nw",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Will List Post",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "list",
                "post",
                "print",
                "comment"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will post it on top of e if i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list which is pushing on top of all accounts.",
                "If i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list.",
                "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                "Or if we click on the list set, we will see that you will see the list on top of it.",
                "On my print, i will post it on top of the list."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will _____  it on top of e if i am going to post it on top of the list, i will post it on top of the list which is pushing on top of all accounts.",
                  "options": [
                    "list",
                    "print",
                    "post",
                    "comment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "post"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If i am going to post it on top of the _____ , i will post it on top of the list.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "print",
                    "list",
                    "post"
                  ],
                  "answer": "list"
                },
                {
                  "question": "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to _____  it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                  "options": [
                    "print",
                    "post",
                    "will",
                    "comment"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Will File Save",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "file",
                "save",
                "koluma",
                "harry"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And i will also get a koluma mode in koluma.",
                "Now, if i want to read a file, then i will get a ried mode in koluma.",
                "Similarly, if i am a type a, i will be a b. then i will show you."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And i will also get a _____  mode in koluma.",
                  "options": [
                    "save",
                    "file",
                    "will",
                    "koluma"
                  ],
                  "answer": "koluma"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, if i want to read a _____ , then i will get a ried mode in koluma.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "file",
                    "koluma",
                    "save"
                  ],
                  "answer": "file"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Will Type Equal",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "type",
                "equal",
                "zero",
                "variable"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will show you that i am a type a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                "Like i am saying, if i am a type d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                "Similarly, if i am a type a, i will be a b. then i will show you.",
                "Now, if i get a friend content, then i will get a content that i will get in this variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you that i am a _____  a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "will",
                    "equal",
                    "variable"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in _____ , you have to use a type of thing.",
                  "options": [
                    "equal",
                    "type",
                    "variable",
                    "zero"
                  ],
                  "answer": "variable"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Like i am saying, if i am a _____  d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                  "options": [
                    "variable",
                    "will",
                    "equal",
                    "type"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "String Play Will",
              "key_points": [
                "string",
                "play",
                "will",
                "function",
                "print"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then you can play a string function.",
                "But if i am a print, i will be a print.",
                "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to print it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                "Then i will be a string variable."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then you can play a string _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "play",
                    "print",
                    "string"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But if i am a _____ , i will be a print.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "play",
                    "function",
                    "print"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                },
                {
                  "question": "1 2 3 4 4 1 5 and if i am going to _____  it, you will see that i will write this list.",
                  "options": [
                    "play",
                    "print",
                    "string",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "print"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "List Change Tuphine",
              "key_points": [
                "list",
                "change",
                "tuphine",
                "type",
                "video"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then i will show you that i am a type a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                "If i change my value to tuphine, i'll change my clothes to 2. if i'm going to have 22, i'll to carry on with me, to have these two colors.",
                "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to type in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                "Like i am saying, if i am a type d liquo, then i will tell you that type is what i have.",
                "This is the list from theinis list i have it was correct vayal limbs!!"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you that i am a _____  a. so, if you are a beginner, then type that i am a type of a type.",
                  "options": [
                    "change",
                    "video",
                    "type",
                    "tuphine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If i _____  my value to tuphine, i'll change my clothes to 2. if i'm going to have 22, i'll to carry on with me, to have these two colors.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "tuphine",
                    "change",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "change"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then i will show you 3.4. so, if you are not going to _____  in variable, you have to use a type of thing.",
                  "options": [
                    "type",
                    "change",
                    "tuphine",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "type"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "bc3317f4-5987-48fd-9432-52c0c8667cb1": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [
        {
          "course_title": "Module 1: introduction to deep learning",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajeTYqhRHno",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Video Deep Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "video",
                "deep",
                "learning",
                "data",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                "And the deep learning job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "If you have a deep learning, you will be interested in this."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this video, i will tell you what _____  learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "deep",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "deep"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the deep _____  job of deep learning is also going to be a big success.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "video",
                    "learning",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine _____ , and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "video",
                    "data",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Talk Data",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "talk",
                "data",
                "many",
                "brain"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how many rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, house price prediction, if you have a lot of data in your house, like this, how _____  rooms, how many bathrooms, how many houses, and how many other sites.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "talk",
                    "brain",
                    "many"
                  ],
                  "answer": "many"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "brain",
                    "talk",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "many",
                    "learning",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Function Data Learning",
              "key_points": [
                "function",
                "data",
                "learning",
                "which",
                "weights"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our data is a function, represents a function.",
                "As we update our weights, we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "That we get a function which will be input in the data as an input layer.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Whenever we talk about learning algorithm, we assume that our _____  is a function, represents a function.",
                  "options": [
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "As we update our _____ , we get the actual idle function which represents that data.",
                  "options": [
                    "weights",
                    "which",
                    "function",
                    "learning"
                  ],
                  "answer": "weights"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, _____  are data that are used in the machine.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "weights",
                    "data",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Good Popular Computer",
              "key_points": [
                "good",
                "popular",
                "computer",
                "cpus",
                "gpus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, cpus, cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                "And the good computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very good.",
                "In this video, i will tell you what deep learning is, why popular is happening and how many years have you been deep learning?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "When i compute cpu, ram and gpus, i am using gpus, _____ , cpus, cpus, i am using this technology.",
                  "options": [
                    "popular",
                    "good",
                    "gpus",
                    "cpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cpus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And the _____  computers that were in the day of the average human was a good computer.",
                  "options": [
                    "cpus",
                    "good",
                    "gpus",
                    "computer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So, the high computer that was in the day of the day of the day is very _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "good",
                    "computer",
                    "gpus",
                    "cpus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "good"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learn Experiment Level",
              "key_points": [
                "learn",
                "experiment",
                "level",
                "will",
                "talk"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And today, we have to learn how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                "In this video, we will talk about this in detail.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                "When we talk about machine learning, then we talk about mathematical algorithms, which are data that are used in the machine.",
                "If i talk about india, then a entry level, deep learning engineer, india's anger comes from the outside."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And today, we have to _____  how to learn how to learn from the game that you have to learn from your back.",
                  "options": [
                    "level",
                    "experiment",
                    "talk",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learn"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this video, we will _____  about this in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "will",
                    "learn"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we _____  about machine learning, and when we talk about deep learning, then fundamentally, there are little differences.",
                  "options": [
                    "talk",
                    "level",
                    "experiment",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "talk"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 2: neural networks basics",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jmmW0F0biz0",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Neural Networks Network",
              "key_points": [
                "neural",
                "networks",
                "network",
                "model",
                "node"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In fact, we should be describing this as an artificial neural network or an a and n to distinguish it from the very unartificial neural network.",
                "And then, finally, number five, there are multiple types of neural networks be on the feed for neural network that we've described here.",
                "Number one, neural networks are composed of node layers.",
                "To illustrate this, let's consider what a single node in our neural network might look like to decide should be go surfing.",
                "Here are five things to note about neural networks in under five minutes."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In fact, we should be describing this as an artificial _____  network or an a and n to distinguish it from the very unartificial neural network.",
                  "options": [
                    "node",
                    "networks",
                    "model",
                    "neural"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And then, finally, number five, there are multiple types of neural _____  be on the feed for neural network that we've described here.",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "node",
                    "networks",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "networks"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Number one, _____  networks are composed of node layers.",
                  "options": [
                    "node",
                    "networks",
                    "neural",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Decision Consider Zero",
              "key_points": [
                "decision",
                "consider",
                "zero",
                "waves",
                "shark"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And then let's consider is it shark free out there.",
                "Now, to each decision, we assign a weight based on its importance on a scale of zero to five.",
                "To illustrate this, let's consider what a single node in our neural network might look like to decide should be go surfing.",
                "The decision to go or not is our predicted outcome or known as our y hat.",
                "Let's assume there are three factors influencing our decision."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And then let's _____  is it shark free out there.",
                  "options": [
                    "decision",
                    "consider",
                    "zero",
                    "waves"
                  ],
                  "answer": "consider"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, to each decision, we assign a weight based on its importance on a scale of _____  to five.",
                  "options": [
                    "zero",
                    "decision",
                    "shark",
                    "consider"
                  ],
                  "answer": "zero"
                },
                {
                  "question": "To illustrate this, let's _____  what a single node in our neural network might look like to decide should be go surfing.",
                  "options": [
                    "shark",
                    "consider",
                    "decision",
                    "waves"
                  ],
                  "answer": "consider"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Give Times Five",
              "key_points": [
                "give",
                "times",
                "five",
                "four",
                "plus"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So y hat equals one times five plus zero times two, plus one times four.",
                "Here are five things to note about neural networks in under five minutes.",
                "Well, we'll give that a score of a four.",
                "So five things in five minutes."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So y hat equals one _____  five plus zero times two, plus one times four.",
                  "options": [
                    "four",
                    "times",
                    "plus",
                    "five"
                  ],
                  "answer": "times"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Here are _____  things to note about neural networks in under five minutes.",
                  "options": [
                    "five",
                    "times",
                    "give",
                    "plus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "five"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Well, we'll give that a score of a _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "plus",
                    "give",
                    "four",
                    "times"
                  ],
                  "answer": "four"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Threshold Different Minus",
              "key_points": [
                "threshold",
                "different",
                "minus",
                "three",
                "gives"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then minus three, that's our threshold.",
                "And if we adjust the weight so the threshold, we can achieve different outcomes.",
                "So each node is composed of input data, weights, a bias or a threshold and then an output.",
                "In what is known as a feed-forward network number three.",
                "Let's assume there are three factors influencing our decision."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then minus _____ , that's our threshold.",
                  "options": [
                    "minus",
                    "three",
                    "gives",
                    "threshold"
                  ],
                  "answer": "three"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And if we adjust the weight so the threshold, we can achieve _____  outcomes.",
                  "options": [
                    "minus",
                    "different",
                    "threshold",
                    "gives"
                  ],
                  "answer": "different"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So each node is composed of input data, weights, a bias or a _____  and then an output.",
                  "options": [
                    "threshold",
                    "gives",
                    "minus",
                    "three"
                  ],
                  "answer": "threshold"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Neural Networks Rnns",
              "key_points": [
                "neural",
                "networks",
                "rnns",
                "future",
                "five"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Here are five things to note about neural networks in under five minutes.",
                "And then, finally, number five, there are multiple types of neural networks be on the feed for neural network that we've described here.",
                "Number one, neural networks are composed of node layers.",
                "And these neural networks reflect the behavior of the human brain, allowing computer programs to recognize patterns and solve common problems in the field of ai and deep learning.",
                "In fact, we should be describing this as an artificial neural network or an a and n to distinguish it from the very unartificial neural network."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Here are five things to note about _____  networks in under five minutes.",
                  "options": [
                    "networks",
                    "neural",
                    "future",
                    "five"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And then, finally, number five, there are multiple types of neural _____  be on the feed for neural network that we've described here.",
                  "options": [
                    "five",
                    "networks",
                    "future",
                    "rnns"
                  ],
                  "answer": "networks"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Number one, _____  networks are composed of node layers.",
                  "options": [
                    "future",
                    "rnns",
                    "neural",
                    "five"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neural"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 3: activation functions",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fu273ovPBmQ",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Activation Functions Look",
              "key_points": [
                "activation",
                "functions",
                "look",
                "different",
                "problem"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Then we have a look at different kinds of activation functions.",
                "Now let's have a look at different kinds of activation functions.",
                "Until now, we have only seen activation functions that output numbers between zero and 1, but this is not a requirement for activation functions.",
                "Now that we've seen different activation functions in theory, let's have a look at how we can use them in tens of flow and pie torch.",
                "There are many different activation functions you can choose."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Then we have a look at _____  kinds of activation functions.",
                  "options": [
                    "problem",
                    "look",
                    "activation",
                    "different"
                  ],
                  "answer": "different"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now let's have a _____  at different kinds of activation functions.",
                  "options": [
                    "look",
                    "functions",
                    "activation",
                    "different"
                  ],
                  "answer": "look"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Until now, we have only seen activation _____  that output numbers between zero and 1, but this is not a requirement for activation functions.",
                  "options": [
                    "problem",
                    "functions",
                    "activation",
                    "different"
                  ],
                  "answer": "functions"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Free Grab Token",
              "key_points": [
                "free",
                "grab",
                "token",
                "link",
                "description"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And if you want to use assembly ai for free, then grab your api token using the link in the description below.",
                "And before you leave, don't forget to grab your free api token using the link in the description below."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And if you want to use assembly ai for free, then _____  your api token using the link in the description below.",
                  "options": [
                    "free",
                    "grab",
                    "token",
                    "description"
                  ],
                  "answer": "grab"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And before you leave, don't forget to grab your _____  api token using the link in the description below.",
                  "options": [
                    "token",
                    "free",
                    "link",
                    "grab"
                  ],
                  "answer": "free"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Input Zero Function",
              "key_points": [
                "input",
                "zero",
                "function",
                "relu",
                "layers"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "It just takes the maximum of zero and the input x. so if the input is negative, it outputs zero and if the input is positive, it simply returns this output without modification.",
                "We'll have a look at the step function, seek-mode, hyperbolic tangent, relu, leaky relu and the softmax.",
                "The step function will just output one if our input is greater than a threshold and zero otherwise.",
                "And for numbers close to zero, we have this rising curve between zero and 1. this again means that the more positive the input number is, the more our neuron will be activated.",
                "It is a scale and shifted seek-mode function that outputs a number between minus 1 and plus 1. relu is probably the most popular choice in hidden layers."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "It just takes the maximum of zero and the _____  x. so if the input is negative, it outputs zero and if the input is positive, it simply returns this output without modification.",
                  "options": [
                    "zero",
                    "layers",
                    "input",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "input"
                },
                {
                  "question": "We'll have a look at the step function, seek-mode, hyperbolic tangent, _____ , leaky relu and the softmax.",
                  "options": [
                    "zero",
                    "function",
                    "input",
                    "relu"
                  ],
                  "answer": "relu"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The step _____  will just output one if our input is greater than a threshold and zero otherwise.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "zero",
                    "relu",
                    "input"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Softmax Probability Relu",
              "key_points": [
                "softmax",
                "probability",
                "relu",
                "last",
                "function"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "We'll have a look at the step function, seek-mode, hyperbolic tangent, relu, leaky relu and the softmax.",
                "In the last function i want to show you is the softmax function.",
                "The seek-mode function is sometimes used in hidden layers, but most of the time it is used in the last layer for binary classification problems.",
                "It is a scale and shifted seek-mode function that outputs a number between minus 1 and plus 1. relu is probably the most popular choice in hidden layers.",
                "So the rule of thumb is that if you are not sure which activation function you should use in your hidden layers, then just use relu."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "We'll have a look at the step _____ , seek-mode, hyperbolic tangent, relu, leaky relu and the softmax.",
                  "options": [
                    "probability",
                    "relu",
                    "last",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In the last _____  i want to show you is the softmax function.",
                  "options": [
                    "probability",
                    "last",
                    "relu",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The seek-mode function is sometimes used in hidden layers, but most of the time it is used in the _____  layer for binary classification problems.",
                  "options": [
                    "last",
                    "probability",
                    "softmax",
                    "function"
                  ],
                  "answer": "last"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Activation Functions Layer",
              "key_points": [
                "activation",
                "functions",
                "layer",
                "them",
                "tens"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For each layer, we can specify the optional argument activation, and then just use the name of the activation function, or we just leave this activation argument away and create the layer ourselves.",
                "Until now, we have only seen activation functions that output numbers between zero and 1, but this is not a requirement for activation functions.",
                "Now that we've seen different activation functions in theory, let's have a look at how we can use them in tens of flow and pie torch.",
                "In pie torch, we also find all activation functions as a layer under torch.nn in our in-in-function of the neural network.",
                "All , so i hope you now have a clear understanding of what activation functions are, until you can use them."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For each _____ , we can specify the optional argument activation, and then just use the name of the activation function, or we just leave this activation argument away and create the layer ourselves.",
                  "options": [
                    "them",
                    "tens",
                    "functions",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "layer"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Until now, we have only seen activation _____  that output numbers between zero and 1, but this is not a requirement for activation functions.",
                  "options": [
                    "them",
                    "functions",
                    "activation",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "functions"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now that we've seen different _____  functions in theory, let's have a look at how we can use them in tens of flow and pie torch.",
                  "options": [
                    "tens",
                    "them",
                    "functions",
                    "activation"
                  ],
                  "answer": "activation"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 4: loss functions",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v_ueBW_5dLg",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Model Loss Five",
              "key_points": [
                "model",
                "loss",
                "five",
                "actual",
                "output"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Five, the model gave us five as the output.",
                "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai model to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                "In machine learning, a loss function tracks the degree of error in the output from an ai model.",
                "If its predictions are inaccurate, let's say it came back with an output of one instead of five, then the loss is larger.",
                "Well, when comparing the model forecasts to the actual number of real youtube views, the model wasn't getting too close."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Five, the model gave us five as the _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "model",
                    "actual",
                    "loss",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "output"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai _____  to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                  "options": [
                    "output",
                    "five",
                    "model",
                    "loss"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In machine learning, a loss function tracks the degree of error in the output from an ai _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "actual",
                    "model",
                    "output",
                    "loss"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Loss Model Function",
              "key_points": [
                "loss",
                "model",
                "function",
                "gradient",
                "some"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Using the gradient of the loss function, optimization algorithms determine which direction to step the model in order to move down the gradient and therefore reduce loss.",
                "Now, that's loss function as an evaluation metric, but it can also be used as input into an algorithm that influences the model parameters to minimize loss, for example, by using gradient descent.",
                "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai model to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                "And at some point we can say that a machine learning model has been sufficiently trained when loss has been minimized, below some predefined threshold.",
                "In machine learning, a loss function tracks the degree of error in the output from an ai model."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Using the gradient of the loss _____ , optimization algorithms determine which direction to step the model in order to move down the gradient and therefore reduce loss.",
                  "options": [
                    "gradient",
                    "function",
                    "loss",
                    "some"
                  ],
                  "answer": "function"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, that's loss function as an evaluation metric, but it can also be used as input into an algorithm that influences the model parameters to minimize loss, for example, by using _____  descent.",
                  "options": [
                    "gradient",
                    "function",
                    "some",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "gradient"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai _____  to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                  "options": [
                    "some",
                    "loss",
                    "function",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Loss Predictions Functions",
              "key_points": [
                "loss",
                "predictions",
                "functions",
                "function",
                "correct"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Unlike regression loss functions, which deal with predicting continuous numerical values, classification loss functions, well, they're focused on determining the accuracy of categorical predictions.",
                "Regression, loss functions and then classification loss functions.",
                "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai model to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                "Now in these cases, the loss function measures how far off the models predictions are from the actual continuous target values.",
                "The loss function provides a numeric value that indicates how far off the models predictions are from the actual results."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Unlike regression loss _____ , which deal with predicting continuous numerical values, classification loss functions, well, they're focused on determining the accuracy of categorical predictions.",
                  "options": [
                    "functions",
                    "predictions",
                    "correct",
                    "loss"
                  ],
                  "answer": "functions"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Regression, _____  functions and then classification loss functions.",
                  "options": [
                    "correct",
                    "loss",
                    "functions",
                    "predictions"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And thanks to _____  function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai model to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                  "options": [
                    "function",
                    "loss",
                    "predictions",
                    "correct"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Loss Value Outliers",
              "key_points": [
                "loss",
                "value",
                "outliers",
                "errors",
                "large"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And squaring the error means the mse gives large mistakes a disproportionately heavy impact on overall loss, which strongly punishes outliers.",
                "And it does this by quantifying the difference or the loss between a predicted value.",
                "Regression, loss functions and then classification loss functions.",
                "Now as its name suggests, mse is calculated as the average of the squared difference between the predicted value and the true value across all training examples.",
                "M-a-e, or mean absolute error, measures the average absolute difference between the predicted value and the actual value."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And squaring the error means the mse gives large mistakes a disproportionately heavy impact on overall _____ , which strongly punishes outliers.",
                  "options": [
                    "value",
                    "outliers",
                    "large",
                    "loss"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And it does this by quantifying the difference or the _____  between a predicted value.",
                  "options": [
                    "outliers",
                    "loss",
                    "errors",
                    "value"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Regression, _____  functions and then classification loss functions.",
                  "options": [
                    "outliers",
                    "loss",
                    "large",
                    "errors"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Loss Labels Entropy",
              "key_points": [
                "loss",
                "labels",
                "entropy",
                "uncertainty",
                "model"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "As such, we can measure the loss in terms of the difference in certainty, we'd have using the ground truth labels to the certainty of the labels predicted by the model.",
                "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai model to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                "Now, cross entropy loss measures how uncertain the model's predictions are compared to the actual outcomes.",
                "Now, that's loss function as an evaluation metric, but it can also be used as input into an algorithm that influences the model parameters to minimize loss, for example, by using gradient descent.",
                "Using the gradient of the loss function, optimization algorithms determine which direction to step the model in order to move down the gradient and therefore reduce loss."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "As such, we can measure the loss in terms of the difference in certainty, we'd have using the ground truth _____  to the certainty of the labels predicted by the model.",
                  "options": [
                    "loss",
                    "labels",
                    "entropy",
                    "uncertainty"
                  ],
                  "answer": "labels"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And thanks to loss function, my colleague can keep tweaking his youtube ai _____  to minimize the loss and teach that model to make better predictions.",
                  "options": [
                    "uncertainty",
                    "loss",
                    "model",
                    "entropy"
                  ],
                  "answer": "model"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, cross entropy _____  measures how uncertain the model's predictions are compared to the actual outcomes.",
                  "options": [
                    "loss",
                    "labels",
                    "uncertainty",
                    "model"
                  ],
                  "answer": "loss"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 5: backpropagation",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ilg3gGewQ5U",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Thing Network Algorithm",
              "key_points": [
                "thing",
                "network",
                "algorithm",
                "neural",
                "what"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "After a quick recap for where we are, the first thing i'll do is an intuitive walkthrough for what the algorithm is doing without any reference to the formulas.",
                "If you watched the last two videos, or if you're just jumping in with the appropriate background, what a neural network is, and how it feeds forward information.",
                "Before that, one thing worth emphasizing is that for this algorithm to work and this goes for all sorts of machine learning beyond just neural networks, you need a lot of training data.",
                "The core algorithm behind how neural networks learn.",
                "But once you unwrap what each part of this algorithm is really doing, each individual effect that it's having is pretty intuitive."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "After a quick recap for where we are, the first thing i'll do is an intuitive walkthrough for _____  the algorithm is doing without any reference to the formulas.",
                  "options": [
                    "thing",
                    "network",
                    "neural",
                    "what"
                  ],
                  "answer": "what"
                },
                {
                  "question": "If you watched the last two videos, or if you're just jumping in with the appropriate background, _____  a neural network is, and how it feeds forward information.",
                  "options": [
                    "neural",
                    "thing",
                    "network",
                    "what"
                  ],
                  "answer": "what"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Before that, one _____  worth emphasizing is that for this algorithm to work and this goes for all sorts of machine learning beyond just neural networks, you need a lot of training data.",
                  "options": [
                    "algorithm",
                    "thing",
                    "neural",
                    "network"
                  ],
                  "answer": "thing"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Cost Each Gradient",
              "key_points": [
                "cost",
                "each",
                "gradient",
                "what",
                "video"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "The magnitude of each component here is telling you how sensitive the cost function is to each weight and bias.",
                "But once you unwrap what each part of this algorithm is really doing, each individual effect that it's having is pretty intuitive.",
                "Back propagation, the topic of this video, is an algorithm for computing that crazy complicated gradient.",
                "So if you were to wiggle that value just a little bit, it's going to cause some change to the cost and that change is 32 times greater than what the same wiggle to that second weight would give.",
                "Remember, when we talk about gradient descent, we don't just care about whether each component should get nudged up or down."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "The magnitude of _____  component here is telling you how sensitive the cost function is to each weight and bias.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "gradient",
                    "cost",
                    "each"
                  ],
                  "answer": "each"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But once you unwrap what _____  part of this algorithm is really doing, each individual effect that it's having is pretty intuitive.",
                  "options": [
                    "cost",
                    "what",
                    "gradient",
                    "each"
                  ],
                  "answer": "each"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Back propagation, the topic of this video, is an algorithm for computing that crazy complicated _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "cost",
                    "what",
                    "each",
                    "gradient"
                  ],
                  "answer": "gradient"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Step Training Example",
              "key_points": [
                "step",
                "training",
                "example",
                "single",
                "every"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "By the way, in practice, it takes computers an extremely long time to add up the influence of every single training example, every single gradient descent step.",
                "Or rather, in principle, it should, but for computational efficiency, we're going to do a little trick later to keep you from needing to hit every single example for every single step.",
                "So i'm going to start things off here with a complete disregard for the notation and just step through those effects that each training example is having on the weights and biases.",
                "And zooming out a bit further, remember that this is all just how a single training example wishes to nudge each one of those weights and biases.",
                "Back propagation is the algorithm for determining how a single training example would like to nudge the weights and biases."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "By the way, in practice, it takes computers an extremely long time to add up the influence of every single training _____ , every single gradient descent step.",
                  "options": [
                    "example",
                    "training",
                    "step",
                    "single"
                  ],
                  "answer": "example"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Or rather, in principle, it should, but for computational efficiency, we're going to do a little trick later to keep you from needing to hit every _____  example for every single step.",
                  "options": [
                    "step",
                    "training",
                    "single",
                    "every"
                  ],
                  "answer": "single"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So i'm going to start things off here with a complete disregard for the notation and just step through those effects that each training _____  is having on the weights and biases.",
                  "options": [
                    "training",
                    "example",
                    "single",
                    "step"
                  ],
                  "answer": "example"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Those Layer Output",
              "key_points": [
                "those",
                "layer",
                "output",
                "weights",
                "last"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And, each of those other output neurons has its own thoughts about what should happen to that second to last layer.",
                "The connections with the best neurons from the preceding layer have the biggest effect since those weights are multiplied by larger activation values.",
                "But, just as with the last layer, it's helpful to just keep a note of what those desire changes are.",
                "So, the desire of this digit tune neuron is added together with the desires of all the other output neurons for what should happen to this second to last layer."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And, each of _____  other output neurons has its own thoughts about what should happen to that second to last layer.",
                  "options": [
                    "those",
                    "weights",
                    "last",
                    "layer"
                  ],
                  "answer": "those"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The connections with the best neurons from the preceding layer have the biggest effect since _____  weights are multiplied by larger activation values.",
                  "options": [
                    "weights",
                    "last",
                    "those",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "those"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But, just as with the _____  layer, it's helpful to just keep a note of what those desire changes are.",
                  "options": [
                    "last",
                    "layer",
                    "weights",
                    "output"
                  ],
                  "answer": "last"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Neurons Increase Weights",
              "key_points": [
                "neurons",
                "increase",
                "weights",
                "activation",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "For example, the increase to that number two neurons activation is in a sense more important than the decrease to the number eight neuron, which is already pretty close to where it should be.",
                "Here, the biggest increases to weights, the biggest strengthening of connections happens between neurons which are the most active, and the ones which we wish to become more active.",
                "The connections with the best neurons from the preceding layer have the biggest effect since those weights are multiplied by larger activation values.",
                "Anyway, the third way that we can help increase this neurons activation is by changing all the activations in the previous layer."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "For example, the increase to that number two _____  activation is in a sense more important than the decrease to the number eight neuron, which is already pretty close to where it should be.",
                  "options": [
                    "weights",
                    "increase",
                    "activation",
                    "neurons"
                  ],
                  "answer": "neurons"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Here, the biggest increases to weights, the biggest strengthening of connections happens between neurons _____  are the most active, and the ones which we wish to become more active.",
                  "options": [
                    "increase",
                    "activation",
                    "which",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The connections with the best neurons from the preceding layer have the biggest effect since those weights are multiplied by larger _____  values.",
                  "options": [
                    "activation",
                    "which",
                    "increase",
                    "weights"
                  ],
                  "answer": "activation"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 6: gradient descent",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U2GullfuAOs",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Alpha Beta Will",
              "key_points": [
                "alpha",
                "beta",
                "will",
                "because",
                "main"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Gaul is fine to alpha and beta because alpha and beta is the main parameter for main variable which change the optimization of the model and these two are the main thing we have to find.",
                "Alpha 1. so the alpha 1 and beta 1 when k is 1. attrition is now 1. so alpha 1 and beta 1 is alpha k and gradient descent of alpha.",
                "Here is a simple linear regression y equal to x plus b and how we can get this linear regression we want to use gradient decendral algorithm to find alpha and beta because alpha and beta.",
                "So for this purpose we will use this or gradient decend and we will put this just substitute this value here alpha x plus beta."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Gaul is fine to _____  and beta because alpha and beta is the main parameter for main variable which change the optimization of the model and these two are the main thing we have to find.",
                  "options": [
                    "main",
                    "because",
                    "will",
                    "alpha"
                  ],
                  "answer": "alpha"
                },
                {
                  "question": "_____  1. so the alpha 1 and beta 1 when k is 1. attrition is now 1. so alpha 1 and beta 1 is alpha k and gradient descent of alpha.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "Alpha",
                    "main",
                    "beta"
                  ],
                  "answer": "Alpha"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Here is a simple linear regression y equal to x plus b and how we can get this linear regression we want to use gradient decendral algorithm to find _____  and beta because alpha and beta.",
                  "options": [
                    "alpha",
                    "beta",
                    "main",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "alpha"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Alpha Beta Gradient",
              "key_points": [
                "alpha",
                "beta",
                "gradient",
                "change",
                "point"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Alpha 1. so the alpha 1 and beta 1 when k is 1. attrition is now 1. so alpha 1 and beta 1 is alpha k and gradient descent of alpha.",
                "It comes to here alpha 1 and beta 1. and then again it comes to here alpha 2 beta 2. so the change gradient shows the direction of change.",
                "Here is a simple linear regression y equal to x plus b and how we can get this linear regression we want to use gradient decendral algorithm to find alpha and beta because alpha and beta.",
                "Gaul is fine to alpha and beta because alpha and beta is the main parameter for main variable which change the optimization of the model and these two are the main thing we have to find."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Alpha 1. so the _____  1 and beta 1 when k is 1. attrition is now 1. so alpha 1 and beta 1 is alpha k and gradient descent of alpha.",
                  "options": [
                    "point",
                    "change",
                    "beta",
                    "alpha"
                  ],
                  "answer": "alpha"
                },
                {
                  "question": "It comes to here alpha 1 and beta 1. and then again it comes to here alpha 2 beta 2. so the _____  gradient shows the direction of change.",
                  "options": [
                    "beta",
                    "change",
                    "point",
                    "gradient"
                  ],
                  "answer": "change"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Here is a simple linear regression y equal to x plus b and how we can get this linear regression we want to use gradient decendral algorithm to find alpha and _____  because alpha and beta.",
                  "options": [
                    "alpha",
                    "change",
                    "beta",
                    "point"
                  ],
                  "answer": "beta"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Minus Alpha Beta",
              "key_points": [
                "minus",
                "alpha",
                "beta",
                "gradient",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Yes this is also minus minus 1 because outside minus so minus minus minus minus minus minus minus to j which substitute the value of j. so to the value of j minus 2 this is.",
                "Alpha 1. so the alpha 1 and beta 1 when k is 1. attrition is now 1. so alpha 1 and beta 1 is alpha k and gradient descent of alpha.",
                "Let's say alpha 0 alpha k minus 2 x y i 2 x minus this one is as we know y i is x alpha x plus b. yes this alpha 0. so we can calculate by putting this value.",
                "Here is a simple linear regression y equal to x plus b and how we can get this linear regression we want to use gradient decendral algorithm to find alpha and beta because alpha and beta."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Yes this is also _____  minus 1 because outside minus so minus minus minus minus minus minus minus to j which substitute the value of j. so to the value of j minus 2 this is.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "minus",
                    "beta",
                    "alpha"
                  ],
                  "answer": "minus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "_____  1. so the alpha 1 and beta 1 when k is 1. attrition is now 1. so alpha 1 and beta 1 is alpha k and gradient descent of alpha.",
                  "options": [
                    "beta",
                    "Alpha",
                    "gradient",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "Alpha"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Let's say _____  0 alpha k minus 2 x y i 2 x minus this one is as we know y i is x alpha x plus b. yes this alpha 0. so we can calculate by putting this value.",
                  "options": [
                    "gradient",
                    "beta",
                    "alpha",
                    "minus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "alpha"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Equal Learning Comes",
              "key_points": [
                "equal",
                "learning",
                "comes",
                "minimum",
                "actual"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And when we are learning from here and come here and finally it comes to almost equal to predicted and actual animals equal.",
                "Once it comes to here alpha 3 beta 3 then it is minimum global minimum.",
                "Then all are equal to 0. so alpha 1 is equal to alpha 0. here is alpha 1 is equal to alpha 0. so there is no change.",
                "It comes to here alpha 1 and beta 1. and then again it comes to here alpha 2 beta 2. so the change gradient shows the direction of change.",
                "Where the actual value and predicted value is almost equal."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And when we are learning from here and come here and finally it comes to almost equal to predicted and _____  animals equal.",
                  "options": [
                    "equal",
                    "learning",
                    "actual",
                    "minimum"
                  ],
                  "answer": "actual"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Once it _____  to here alpha 3 beta 3 then it is minimum global minimum.",
                  "options": [
                    "equal",
                    "learning",
                    "comes",
                    "minimum"
                  ],
                  "answer": "comes"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Then all are _____  to 0. so alpha 1 is equal to alpha 0. here is alpha 1 is equal to alpha 0. so there is no change.",
                  "options": [
                    "minimum",
                    "comes",
                    "learning",
                    "equal"
                  ],
                  "answer": "equal"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Same Equation Plus",
              "key_points": [
                "same",
                "equation",
                "plus",
                "method",
                "extra"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Like it can be this is linear equation it may be quadratic equation by equal to x k r plus a x plus b. so you will use same method with the extra.",
                "So you can you you can consider this one and same do same method.",
                "So we repeat from here beta and to j here is same alpha x plus beta gradient of beta.",
                "Here is a simple linear regression y equal to x plus b and how we can get this linear regression we want to use gradient decendral algorithm to find alpha and beta because alpha and beta.",
                "So we will use for this loss function which is called cos function also are residual, secure some and this y had is equal same as this one."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Like it can be this is linear _____  it may be quadratic equation by equal to x k r plus a x plus b. so you will use same method with the extra.",
                  "options": [
                    "equation",
                    "extra",
                    "plus",
                    "method"
                  ],
                  "answer": "equation"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So you can you you can consider this one and _____  do same method.",
                  "options": [
                    "extra",
                    "same",
                    "method",
                    "plus"
                  ],
                  "answer": "same"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So we repeat from here beta and to j here is _____  alpha x plus beta gradient of beta.",
                  "options": [
                    "extra",
                    "equation",
                    "same",
                    "method"
                  ],
                  "answer": "same"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 7: cnn basics",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zfiSAzpy9NM",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Koala Will Image",
              "key_points": [
                "koala",
                "will",
                "image",
                "these",
                "filter"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "It will say if in the image you are seeing koala's eye nose and ears it means there is a koala's face in the image.",
                "Using that it will use back propagation and it will figure out the amount of filters it will figure out the values in this filter and that is part of the learning or the back propagation.",
                "When we look at koala's image we look at the little features like this round eyes, this black prominent flat nose, this fluffy ears and we detect these features one by one.",
                "In our brain there are different set up neurons working on these different features and they're firing they're saying yeah i found koala's ears yes i found koala's nose and so on.",
                "So we take our original image and we will apply a convolution operation or a filter operation."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "It will say if in the image you are seeing _____ 's eye nose and ears it means there is a koala's face in the image.",
                  "options": [
                    "filter",
                    "image",
                    "will",
                    "koala"
                  ],
                  "answer": "koala"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Using that it will use back propagation and it will figure out the amount of _____ s it will figure out the values in this filter and that is part of the learning or the back propagation.",
                  "options": [
                    "image",
                    "koala",
                    "will",
                    "filter"
                  ],
                  "answer": "filter"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When we look at koala's image we look at the little features like this round eyes, this black prominent flat nose, this fluffy ears and we detect _____  features one by one.",
                  "options": [
                    "these",
                    "koala",
                    "filter",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "these"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Network Neural Will",
              "key_points": [
                "network",
                "neural",
                "will",
                "convolution",
                "part"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In that you will have typically a convolution and a new layer then you will have pulling then there will be another convolution, a new pulling.",
                "The network will learn those on its own and that is the most fascinating part about neural network in general.",
                "Here the first part where we use convolutional neural convolution operation is feature extraction part.",
                "There could be a number of layers for convolution and pulling and in the end you will have fully connected dense neural network.",
                "Using that it will use back propagation and it will figure out the amount of filters it will figure out the values in this filter and that is part of the learning or the back propagation."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In that you will have typically a _____  and a new layer then you will have pulling then there will be another convolution, a new pulling.",
                  "options": [
                    "network",
                    "convolution",
                    "part",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "convolution"
                },
                {
                  "question": "The network will learn those on its own and that is the most fascinating _____  about neural network in general.",
                  "options": [
                    "convolution",
                    "part",
                    "will",
                    "neural"
                  ],
                  "answer": "part"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Here the first part where we use _____ al neural convolution operation is feature extraction part.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "convolution",
                    "network",
                    "neural"
                  ],
                  "answer": "convolution"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Image Corner Still",
              "key_points": [
                "image",
                "corner",
                "still",
                "size",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "If you have koala's face in a left corner versus corner it is still a koala.",
                "You're still getting same size of image.",
                "Here we have a filter which we move around the image and at a time we are talking about only a local region so we are not affecting the whole image.",
                "But when you have a bigger image let's say this little cute looking koala they may size this 1920 by 1080 we have 3 as rgb channel here one for red, green and blue.",
                "So if the pixels are moved around it should still be able to detect the object in an image but with a nn it's hard."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "If you have koala's face in a left _____  versus corner it is still a koala.",
                  "options": [
                    "corner",
                    "size",
                    "image",
                    "still"
                  ],
                  "answer": "corner"
                },
                {
                  "question": "You're still getting same size of _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "size",
                    "still",
                    "image"
                  ],
                  "answer": "image"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Here we have a filter _____  we move around the image and at a time we are talking about only a local region so we are not affecting the whole image.",
                  "options": [
                    "image",
                    "size",
                    "which",
                    "corner"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Feature Number Pulling",
              "key_points": [
                "feature",
                "number",
                "pulling",
                "stride",
                "window"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Well you can do a stride of 1. in this case we did 2 by 2 window and stride of 2. stride of 2 means once we are done with this window we move 2 points further.",
                "So here you take a window of 2 by 2 and you pick the maximum number from that window and put it here.",
                "Similarly here maximum number in green window is 3. so put 3. so you take the feature map.",
                "Apply your pulling and generate a new feature map after the pulling.",
                "When our number is shifted so see this is the original number where we got this max pulling map."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Well you can do a _____  of 1. in this case we did 2 by 2 window and stride of 2. stride of 2 means once we are done with this window we move 2 points further.",
                  "options": [
                    "stride",
                    "feature",
                    "pulling",
                    "window"
                  ],
                  "answer": "stride"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So here you take a _____  of 2 by 2 and you pick the maximum number from that window and put it here.",
                  "options": [
                    "window",
                    "feature",
                    "pulling",
                    "number"
                  ],
                  "answer": "window"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Similarly here maximum number in green _____  is 3. so put 3. so you take the feature map.",
                  "options": [
                    "window",
                    "number",
                    "feature",
                    "stride"
                  ],
                  "answer": "window"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Learning Video Deep",
              "key_points": [
                "learning",
                "video",
                "deep",
                "tutorial",
                "series"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "I'm continuing my deep learning tutorial series now and my goal is to finish all the topics in deep learning including convolution neural networks, rnns, language models and so on.",
                "Which is nothing but if you have seen my activation video on the same deep learning tutorial series.",
                "In this deep learning series we have already looked at artificial neural network video on handwritten digits or recognizations.",
                "So if you see my previous videos in this deep learning tutorial series you will get an idea on why it brings the non-linearity.",
                "Especially see the video on the activations in the same tutorial series."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "I'm continuing my deep learning tutorial _____  now and my goal is to finish all the topics in deep learning including convolution neural networks, rnns, language models and so on.",
                  "options": [
                    "learning",
                    "tutorial",
                    "series",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "series"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which is nothing but if you have seen my activation _____  on the same deep learning tutorial series.",
                  "options": [
                    "deep",
                    "tutorial",
                    "learning",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "video"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In this deep _____  series we have already looked at artificial neural network video on handwritten digits or recognizations.",
                  "options": [
                    "tutorial",
                    "learning",
                    "series",
                    "deep"
                  ],
                  "answer": "learning"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 8: rnn and lstm",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LfnrRPFhkuY",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Which Word They",
              "key_points": [
                "which",
                "word",
                "they",
                "memory",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Now hidden state, which is short term memory, and there is a self state, which is a long term memory.",
                "And when you multiply that with previous memory, which is previous cell state, you have a vector of less or zero zero zero, and you have another vector, which is a memory of previous cell state.",
                "Now to predict this word, need, it needs to know about the word today, which appear at the very beginning of the sentence.",
                "They have a very short term memory of just few words, which are like nearby.",
                "What if we build this long-term memory along with short-term memory in such a way that we store the meaningful words or the key words into this long-term memory?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Now hidden state, _____  is short term memory, and there is a self state, which is a long term memory.",
                  "options": [
                    "memory",
                    "which",
                    "they",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And when you multiply that with previous _____ , which is previous cell state, you have a vector of less or zero zero zero, and you have another vector, which is a memory of previous cell state.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "they",
                    "word",
                    "memory"
                  ],
                  "answer": "memory"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now to predict this _____ , need, it needs to know about the word today, which appear at the very beginning of the sentence.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "memory",
                    "word",
                    "they"
                  ],
                  "answer": "word"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Memory State Term",
              "key_points": [
                "memory",
                "state",
                "term",
                "will",
                "which"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Now hidden state, which is short term memory, and there is a self state, which is a long term memory.",
                "And when you multiply that with previous memory, which is previous cell state, you have a vector of less or zero zero zero, and you have another vector, which is a memory of previous cell state.",
                "Now if you want to remember, long term memory, we need to introduce another state called a long term memory.",
                "And this square box is called a memory cell, because this hidden state is containing the short term memory.",
                "Whatever is the output, you take that, and then you take long term memory, apply tan edge, and you multiply that, and you will get your hidden state."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Now hidden state, _____  is short term memory, and there is a self state, which is a long term memory.",
                  "options": [
                    "term",
                    "memory",
                    "which",
                    "state"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And when you multiply that with previous memory, which is previous cell _____ , you have a vector of less or zero zero zero, and you have another vector, which is a memory of previous cell state.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "state",
                    "which",
                    "term"
                  ],
                  "answer": "state"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now if you want to remember, long _____  memory, we need to introduce another state called a long term memory.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "term",
                    "state",
                    "memory"
                  ],
                  "answer": "term"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Cuisine When Words",
              "key_points": [
                "cuisine",
                "when",
                "words",
                "memory",
                "will"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "What if we build this long-term memory along with short-term memory in such a way that we store the meaningful words or the key words into this long-term memory?",
                "When you are at here, cuisine is, it will remember is and cuisine.",
                "And when i go all the way here, now when i have to make a prediction on cuisine, i have that memory that this, we are talking about samusa and hence it has to be indian.",
                "Well obviously indian, someos is an indian cuisine, so you will say his favorite cuisine is indian.",
                "When you are processing the sentence, which words told you that this will be a good idea."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "What if we build this long-term memory along with short-term memory in such a way that we store the meaningful _____  or the key words into this long-term memory?",
                  "options": [
                    "words",
                    "when",
                    "will",
                    "cuisine"
                  ],
                  "answer": "words"
                },
                {
                  "question": "When you are at here, _____  is, it will remember is and cuisine.",
                  "options": [
                    "memory",
                    "will",
                    "cuisine",
                    "when"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cuisine"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And when i go all the way here, now when i have to make a prediction on _____ , i have that memory that this, we are talking about samusa and hence it has to be indian.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "cuisine",
                    "words",
                    "memory"
                  ],
                  "answer": "cuisine"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Pastas When Will",
              "key_points": [
                "pastas",
                "when",
                "will",
                "memory",
                "cheese"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "And then in then, when you are about to be asked, , what is your answer for autocomplete, you will say italian because you have the memory of pastas and cheese.",
                "What if we build this long-term memory along with short-term memory in such a way that we store the meaningful words or the key words into this long-term memory?",
                "But when you find things like samusa, it will store it in a long-term memory, see?",
                "And when i go all the way here, now when i have to make a prediction on cuisine, i have that memory that this, we are talking about samusa and hence it has to be indian.",
                "When you encounter, let's say samusa, you will store samusa in your long term memory."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "And then in then, when you are about to be asked, , what is your answer for autocomplete, you will say italian because you have the memory of _____  and cheese.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "pastas",
                    "memory",
                    "when"
                  ],
                  "answer": "pastas"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What if we build this long-term _____  along with short-term memory in such a way that we store the meaningful words or the key words into this long-term memory?",
                  "options": [
                    "pastas",
                    "memory",
                    "when",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "memory"
                },
                {
                  "question": "But when you find things like samusa, it will store it in a long-term _____ , see?",
                  "options": [
                    "pastas",
                    "memory",
                    "when",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "memory"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Will Weight Doing",
              "key_points": [
                "will",
                "weight",
                "doing",
                "when",
                "past"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So when past the game, not only you forgot about samusa, you need to add a memory of past that.",
                "So when you're doing, by the way, these vectors will have weights here.",
                "So there will be some weight here, some weight here.",
                "So in this function what you're doing is, ht minus 1 into that weight plus, xt into that weight plus bias, and then you're applying tan edge on top of it.",
                "So when you have a word, for example, you will first convert into a vector."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So when _____  the game, not only you forgot about samusa, you need to add a memory of past that.",
                  "options": [
                    "weight",
                    "past",
                    "doing",
                    "when"
                  ],
                  "answer": "past"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So when you're _____ , by the way, these vectors will have weights here.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "past",
                    "doing",
                    "when"
                  ],
                  "answer": "doing"
                },
                {
                  "question": "So there will be some _____  here, some weight here.",
                  "options": [
                    "will",
                    "when",
                    "doing",
                    "weight"
                  ],
                  "answer": "weight"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "course_title": "Module 9: transformers introduction",
          "source": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BjRVS2wTtcA",
          "lessons": [
            {
              "lesson_number": 1,
              "lesson_title": "Transformers Will Data",
              "key_points": [
                "transformers",
                "will",
                "data",
                "image",
                "video"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "In this video we will continue to keep our deep learning playlist and finally we will cover up all the things that i had asked for in every next few days you guys did ?",
                "Image based data, cnn, sequentially data, rnn and so on.",
                "Because, in the next video, we are going to cover a topic called self-attention, which is like the center of transformers, transformers, which are the most important mechanisms in the game.",
                "Just like it takes to generate, image, video, genre.",
                "After that, since transformers are multi-model, you can see the same thing in image domain."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "In this _____  we will continue to keep our deep learning playlist and finally we will cover up all the things that i had asked for in every next few days you guys did ?",
                  "options": [
                    "data",
                    "will",
                    "video",
                    "image"
                  ],
                  "answer": "video"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Image based _____ , cnn, sequentially data, rnn and so on.",
                  "options": [
                    "image",
                    "will",
                    "data",
                    "video"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Because, in the next video, we are going to cover a topic called self-attention, which is like the center of _____ , transformers, which are the most important mechanisms in the game.",
                  "options": [
                    "video",
                    "transformers",
                    "data",
                    "will"
                  ],
                  "answer": "transformers"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 2,
              "lesson_title": "Architecture Transformers Which",
              "key_points": [
                "architecture",
                "transformers",
                "which",
                "data",
                "train"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Which is why you can train this architecture very big data sets.",
                "Because, in the next video, we are going to cover a topic called self-attention, which is like the center of transformers, transformers, which are the most important mechanisms in the game.",
                "Now, if i can't train a very big data sets, then, the problem is, the problem is that, we, can't train the transfer learning technique here.",
                "Because you have a architecture, a very big data set to train.",
                "Training if we slow, so by definition, we have huge data sets like tb's of data, we can't train our model."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Which is why you can train this architecture very big _____  sets.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "train",
                    "architecture",
                    "data"
                  ],
                  "answer": "data"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Because, in the next video, we are going to cover a topic called self-attention, which is like the center of _____ , transformers, which are the most important mechanisms in the game.",
                  "options": [
                    "architecture",
                    "which",
                    "transformers",
                    "train"
                  ],
                  "answer": "transformers"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Now, if i can't _____  a very big data sets, then, the problem is, the problem is that, we, can't train the transfer learning technique here.",
                  "options": [
                    "transformers",
                    "train",
                    "data",
                    "architecture"
                  ],
                  "answer": "train"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 3,
              "lesson_title": "Transformers Future Recently",
              "key_points": [
                "transformers",
                "future",
                "recently",
                "other",
                "result"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "But just wanted to give you an origin story of how transformers came into being, that the factors that were pushed, transformers created and this entire thing is exactly executed.",
                "Transformers concept, different domains may introduce to a, this was the time jump, vision transformers, a couple of jobs.",
                "Just like every other deep learning architecture, transformers are limited.",
                "They have to use the other company or the other website.",
                "And hopefully, future will see more powerful transformers."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "But just wanted to give you an origin story of how _____  came into being, that the factors that were pushed, transformers created and this entire thing is exactly executed.",
                  "options": [
                    "result",
                    "transformers",
                    "recently",
                    "future"
                  ],
                  "answer": "transformers"
                },
                {
                  "question": "_____  concept, different domains may introduce to a, this was the time jump, vision transformers, a couple of jobs.",
                  "options": [
                    "Transformers",
                    "other",
                    "result",
                    "future"
                  ],
                  "answer": "Transformers"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Just like every _____  deep learning architecture, transformers are limited.",
                  "options": [
                    "result",
                    "future",
                    "transformers",
                    "other"
                  ],
                  "answer": "other"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 4,
              "lesson_title": "Paper Which Transformers",
              "key_points": [
                "paper",
                "which",
                "transformers",
                "architecture",
                "transformer"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "Because, in the next video, we are going to cover a topic called self-attention, which is like the center of transformers, transformers, which are the most important mechanisms in the game.",
                "In 2017, this paper came and transformed the architecture of this paper.",
                "Aariga plan is to create a transformation in three-ray chart, which is in architecture, which is in detail.",
                "Rather than going for different architectures, we are seeing that all the type of problems we have to solve for a single architecture and that is the transformers.",
                "What were those factors that create this requirement of creating a transformers' architecture?"
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "Because, in the next video, we are going to cover a topic called self-attention, _____  is like the center of transformers, transformers, which are the most important mechanisms in the game.",
                  "options": [
                    "architecture",
                    "which",
                    "transformer",
                    "transformers"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In 2017, this _____  came and transformed the architecture of this paper.",
                  "options": [
                    "transformer",
                    "architecture",
                    "transformers",
                    "paper"
                  ],
                  "answer": "paper"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Aariga plan is to create a transformation in three-ray chart, _____  is in architecture, which is in detail.",
                  "options": [
                    "which",
                    "transformer",
                    "transformers",
                    "paper"
                  ],
                  "answer": "which"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "lesson_number": 5,
              "lesson_title": "Context Vector Sentence",
              "key_points": [
                "context",
                "vector",
                "sentence",
                "decoder",
                "need"
              ],
              "notes": [
                "So, this architecture has changed a little earlier in the earlier way that you have to detect the context vector on the , and then, in the decoder times, the context vector has been sent.",
                "Like, if i print light, in the context vector, a 4-kv, a 3-kv, a 2-kv, a 3-kv, but if i print a c2, then a 3-2, a 3-kv, a 3-kv, a 3-kv, a 3-kv, a 4-kv, so , my context vector is a weighted sum.",
                "And, as per the sentence, we give a context vector.",
                "Like this context vector is a representation of this entire sentence.",
                "Now, let's pass this context vector in decoder."
              ],
              "quiz": [
                {
                  "question": "So, this architecture has changed a little earlier in the earlier way that you have to detect the context _____  on the , and then, in the decoder times, the context vector has been sent.",
                  "options": [
                    "vector",
                    "context",
                    "need",
                    "decoder"
                  ],
                  "answer": "vector"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Like, if i print light, in the context _____ , a 4-kv, a 3-kv, a 2-kv, a 3-kv, but if i print a c2, then a 3-2, a 3-kv, a 3-kv, a 3-kv, a 3-kv, a 4-kv, so , my context vector is a weighted sum.",
                  "options": [
                    "need",
                    "sentence",
                    "vector",
                    "decoder"
                  ],
                  "answer": "vector"
                },
                {
                  "question": "And, as per the sentence, we give a context _____ .",
                  "options": [
                    "context",
                    "vector",
                    "need",
                    "decoder"
                  ],
                  "answer": "vector"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "1ceb804b-b544-48cd-8312-271e3a97f2af": {
    "status": "processing",
    "result": null,
    "error": null
  },
  "49eb2d5f-f39a-4582-aeb6-26ca00643620": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "1a08d753-9dff-45e3-86c1-7eb57521c7c7": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "972bec59-e585-40a9-b16f-526c0abd4750": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "a1335734-4fd4-40fa-bd51-f08136916c7f": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "bb8875e6-e028-4b38-9633-67f16e470f10": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "afd2a61a-696c-4c37-a3e0-d1fa865b247d": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "0aa87435-a487-4814-af0d-15ebe477f427": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "039dfb37-5709-4805-9347-3e69798f3ded": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "All videos failed transcript extraction"
  },
  "b1d29c4a-bee2-43f2-bc94-144acc98cbed": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "a99c1606-7d5d-4ae6-a211-8203ad0cd07c": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "76e0c3a5-c71b-4a5d-ad35-a233bfcb4315": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "f28538ee-0e9d-4b88-9c6f-b20ba7e10e6e": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "5582bd2e-d7e2-4ef6-a59f-87186025fa7c": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "7a8aac00-9704-4525-8ac5-0229a5aacd18": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "b9c84cfa-85e4-45a6-9820-54783600bdb5": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "618c43b0-4340-4cd3-92b8-031eb41eef79": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "f5d2edcf-0659-49ba-9e7d-65049d0463fa": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "cea0b373-f277-4730-a3cf-b651f16e2424": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "8ebda9a1-86d5-4764-87a8-6f757a389d6f": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "10eae5a0-840c-475f-8b3f-12837c37ddf3": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "2f2be4c6-2b1e-471a-9436-599fb22c0f71": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "6ae4c8bf-14c9-4d95-b726-8103fbb28044": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "c3c61dbd-b5ab-47a9-97db-78580b11bc36": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "8b19d814-3fe0-4f3c-b45b-8758688798b7": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "8f0a5028-183f-49e5-b57d-53782de8dd40": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "c2998e5d-49f5-421f-927d-aa73caeb3018": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "44877cc9-0efe-4add-85b1-f4c070330353": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "0e96e252-5bda-43d2-8ece-3c12c7c8e127": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "c12b5a48-f113-44a1-808f-033bc52161f0": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "c8823e9f-7eff-41a1-b3d7-ea942dc2621a": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "f546a840-6db1-4a9d-b57b-9d868bd83cf1": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "5073845b-3121-4938-b006-63e508e3c67f": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "0aa75a76-1973-4e8c-bd29-1e31a9db06b5": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "567f3a37-7611-412b-94e0-ec445a01e7e2": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "beginner",
      "modules": [],
      "recommendations": {
        "udemy": [
          {
            "title": "Deep Learning Masterclass",
            "url": "https://www.udemy.com/"
          }
        ],
        "coursera": [
          {
            "title": "Deep Learning Specialization",
            "url": "https://www.coursera.org/"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "5e5a0524-7308-488a-bc6f-04ff98094601": {
    "status": "completed",
    "result": {
      "course_title": "Deep Learning (Beginner)",
      "difficulty": "Beginner",
      "modules": [],
      "recommendations": {
        "udemy": [
          {
            "title": "Deep Learning Masterclass",
            "url": "https://www.udemy.com/"
          }
        ],
        "coursera": [
          {
            "title": "Deep Learning Specialization",
            "url": "https://www.coursera.org/"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "error": null
  },
  "f0ba1941-d09f-4a6f-9a10-67803ed4f93d": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "72be6919-a1a1-4a7c-b190-e17915e55f65": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "a84a49cb-6002-4b63-a4a2-4248576ec28f": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "b7d9152b-c398-48c5-a86e-aaa3ecbdcdfb": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "72b28c5f-e31f-4f60-894e-04760f024d3f": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "d7a09ec1-c3b8-457e-bb00-6d9220399803": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "f2e27378-37b8-4150-81bb-23d492e4dd08": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "64640232-01df-40ad-bd18-f08c1464b6ae": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "7a3d3ba9-8fd5-4232-a05d-804b3786404c": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  },
  "42480889-7b43-4b2f-99e1-d6ae309dbeaa": {
    "status": "failed",
    "result": null,
    "error": "build_course_from_topic() got an unexpected keyword argument 'videos_per_topic'"
  }
}